<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en"><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.3.4">Jekyll</generator><link href="https://family-fantasy-football.github.io/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml"/><link href="https://family-fantasy-football.github.io/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" hreflang="en"/><updated>2024-12-12T05:49:59+00:00</updated><id>https://family-fantasy-football.github.io/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Family Fantasy Football League</title><entry><title type="html">Week 15 Matchups Preview</title><link href="https://family-fantasy-football.github.io/blog/2024/Week-15_preview/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Week 15 Matchups Preview"/><published>2024-12-12T03:52:32+00:00</published><updated>2024-12-12T03:52:32+00:00</updated><id>https://family-fantasy-football.github.io/blog/2024/Week-15_preview</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://family-fantasy-football.github.io/blog/2024/Week-15_preview/"><![CDATA[<h2 id="matchups">Matchups</h2> <h3 id="tom-and-jerry--pink-pony-club">Tom and Jerry @ Pink Pony Club</h3> <p><strong>Projected Score:</strong> Tom and Jerry 283.52 - 316.93 Pink Pony Club</p> <p><strong>Historical Matchup:</strong> 2-0 (Avg Score: Pink Pony Club wins by 153.6-135.0)</p> <h4 id="position-breakdown">Position Breakdown</h4> <table> <tr><th>Position</th><th>Away</th><th>Advantage</th><th>Home</th></tr> <tr><td>QB</td><td>17.7</td><td>➡️</td><td>20.6</td></tr> <tr><td>RB</td><td>14.0</td><td>➡️</td><td>14.9</td></tr> <tr><td>TE</td><td>8.1</td><td>➡️</td><td>6.0</td></tr> <tr><td>WR</td><td>10.5</td><td>➡️</td><td>11.1</td></tr> </table> <p><br/></p> <h4 id="injury-report">Injury Report</h4> <p><strong>Pink Pony Club:</strong> Evan Engram (Questionable), Isaac Guerendo (Questionable),</p> <p><strong>Tom and Jerry:</strong> Alvin Kamara (Questionable), Chris Olave (Injured Reserve), Austin Ekeler (Injured Reserve),</p> <hr/> <h3 id="who-killed-charbonnet-ramsey--hamlin-my-business">Who Killed Charbonnet Ramsey? @ Hamlin My Business</h3> <p><strong>Projected Score:</strong> Who Killed Charbonnet Ramsey? 317.41 - 277.94 Hamlin My Business</p> <p><strong>Historical Matchup:</strong> 1-1 (Avg Score: Who Killed Charbonnet Ramsey? wins by 138.2-143.2)</p> <h4 id="position-breakdown-1">Position Breakdown</h4> <table> <tr><th>Position</th><th>Away</th><th>Advantage</th><th>Home</th></tr> <tr><td>QB</td><td>20.0</td><td>➡️</td><td>20.3</td></tr> <tr><td>RB</td><td>12.7</td><td>➡️</td><td>12.9</td></tr> <tr><td>TE</td><td>10.6</td><td>➡️</td><td>11.6</td></tr> <tr><td>WR</td><td>12.3</td><td>➡️</td><td>11.4</td></tr> </table> <p><br/></p> <h4 id="injury-report-1">Injury Report</h4> <p><strong>Hamlin My Business :</strong> Joe Burrow (Questionable), Ladd McConkey (Questionable), Demarcus Robinson (Questionable), Tyreek Hill (Questionable), Malik Nabers (Questionable),</p> <p><strong>Who Killed Charbonnet Ramsey?:</strong> Josh Downs (Questionable),</p> <hr/> <h3 id="hit-and-ruggs--to-infinity-and-bijan">Hit and Ruggs @ To Infinity and Bijan!</h3> <p><strong>Projected Score:</strong> Hit and Ruggs 246.02 - 225.30 To Infinity and Bijan!</p> <p><strong>Historical Matchup:</strong> 0-3 (Avg Score: Hit and Ruggs wins by 105.2-147.5)</p> <h4 id="position-breakdown-2">Position Breakdown</h4> <table> <tr><th>Position</th><th>Away</th><th>Advantage</th><th>Home</th></tr> <tr><td>QB</td><td>16.2</td><td>➡️</td><td>15.2</td></tr> <tr><td>RB</td><td>12.9</td><td>➡️</td><td>12.8</td></tr> <tr><td>TE</td><td>10.7</td><td>➡️</td><td>8.5</td></tr> <tr><td>WR</td><td>11.9</td><td>➡️</td><td>10.2</td></tr> </table> <p><br/></p> <h4 id="injury-report-2">Injury Report</h4> <p><strong>To Infinity and Bijan!:</strong> Raheem Mostert (Questionable), Kenneth Walker III (Questionable), Mike Evans (Questionable),</p> <p><strong>Hit and Ruggs:</strong> Trey McBride (Questionable), Diontae Johnson (Suspension), Jaylen Waddle (Questionable), Breece Hall (Questionable), Dallas Goedert (Injured Reserve),</p> <hr/> <h3 id="abbey-road-to-victory--mama-daughter-duo">Abbey Road to Victory @ Mama Daughter Duo</h3> <p><strong>Projected Score:</strong> Abbey Road to Victory 235.60 - 263.36 Mama Daughter Duo</p> <p><strong>Historical Matchup:</strong> 2-1 (Avg Score: Mama Daughter Duo wins by 127.8-104.9)</p> <h4 id="position-breakdown-3">Position Breakdown</h4> <table> <tr><th>Position</th><th>Away</th><th>Advantage</th><th>Home</th></tr> <tr><td>QB</td><td>15.1</td><td>➡️</td><td>16.4</td></tr> <tr><td>RB</td><td>11.1</td><td>➡️</td><td>11.7</td></tr> <tr><td>TE</td><td>8.2</td><td>➡️</td><td>10.2</td></tr> <tr><td>WR</td><td>9.9</td><td>➡️</td><td>10.4</td></tr> </table> <p><br/></p> <h4 id="injury-report-3">Injury Report</h4> <p><strong>Mama Daughter Duo:</strong> David Njoku (Questionable), Derek Carr (Questionable),</p> <p><strong>Abbey Road to Victory:</strong> Alexander Mattison (Questionable), Tony Pollard (Questionable),</p> <hr/> <h3 id="fantasy-guru-kayden--michaels-managable-team">Fantasy Guru Kayden @ Michael’s Managable Team</h3> <p><strong>Projected Score:</strong> Fantasy Guru Kayden 234.51 - 186.18 Michael’s Managable Team</p> <p><strong>Historical Matchup:</strong> 1-2 (Avg Score: Fantasy Guru Kayden wins by 97.2-130.8)</p> <h4 id="position-breakdown-4">Position Breakdown</h4> <table> <tr><th>Position</th><th>Away</th><th>Advantage</th><th>Home</th></tr> <tr><td>QB</td><td>17.9</td><td>⬅️</td><td>13.2</td></tr> <tr><td>RB</td><td>11.5</td><td>➡️</td><td>14.0</td></tr> <tr><td>TE</td><td>8.2</td><td>➡️</td><td>7.9</td></tr> <tr><td>WR</td><td>10.1</td><td>➡️</td><td>9.7</td></tr> </table> <p><br/></p> <h4 id="injury-report-4">Injury Report</h4> <p><strong>Michael’s Managable Team:</strong> CeeDee Lamb (Questionable), Hollywood Brown (Injured Reserve), Justin Herbert (Questionable),</p> <p><strong>Fantasy Guru Kayden:</strong> Zamir White (Injured Reserve), George Pickens (Questionable), Sterling Shepard (Questionable), Bucky Irving (Questionable),</p> <hr/>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="league-previews"/><category term="2024-25,"/><category term="WeeklyPreview,"/><category term="Week15"/><summary type="html"><![CDATA[preview of next weeks matchups]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Abbey Road to Victory Week 14 Report</title><link href="https://family-fantasy-football.github.io/blog/2024/Week-14-ARV/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Abbey Road to Victory Week 14 Report"/><published>2024-12-10T22:19:38+00:00</published><updated>2024-12-10T22:19:38+00:00</updated><id>https://family-fantasy-football.github.io/blog/2024/Week-14-ARV</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://family-fantasy-football.github.io/blog/2024/Week-14-ARV/"><![CDATA[<h2 id="week-at-a-glance">Week at a Glance</h2> <p>Abbey Road to Victory Lost against Mama Daughter Duo 108.02-131.46<br/> Current Standing: #8<br/> Playoff Chances: 0.0%<br/> Lineup Efficiency: 86.9%<br/> Best Performer: Kyler Murray (17.96 pts)<br/></p> <pre><code class="language-echarts">{
    "tooltip": {
        "trigger": "item",
        "formatter": "{a} &lt;br/&gt;{b}: {d}%"
    },
    "legend": {
        "orient": "vertical",
        "left": "left",
        "data": [
            "QB",
            "RB",
            "WR",
            "TE",
            "D/ST",
            "K"
        ]
    },
    "series": [
        {
            "name": "Position Points",
            "type": "pie",
            "radius": [
                "50%",
                "70%"
            ],
            "avoidLabelOverlap": false,
            "data": [
                {
                    "value": 27.7,
                    "name": "QB"
                },
                {
                    "value": 39.9,
                    "name": "RB"
                },
                {
                    "value": 33.4,
                    "name": "WR"
                },
                {
                    "value": 7.0,
                    "name": "TE"
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}
</code></pre> <h2 id="player-report">Player Report</h2> <h4 id="kyler-murray-qb">Kyler Murray (QB)</h4> <p><strong>Injury Status:</strong> Active <br/> <strong>Lineup Slot:</strong> QB <br/> <strong>Details:</strong> Murray threw a 41-yard touchdown pass to Michael Wilson on the opening drive, but the quarterback was picked off on the next two possessions, which helped Seattle build a 24-10 halftime lead. Murray closed the gap to 27-18 in the third quarter with a two-yard touchdown pass to James Conner followed by a Murray rush for a two-point conversion, but that’s as close as Arizona would get. While Murray tossed multiple touchdown passes for only the third time this season, he also finished with multiple interceptions for the second consecutive game after having no multi-interception games through Week 12. He’ll look to clean up the mistakes in Week 15 against the Patriots.</p> <h4 id="kirk-cousins-qb">Kirk Cousins (QB)</h4> <p><strong>Injury Status:</strong> Active <br/> <strong>Lineup Slot:</strong> OP <br/> <strong>Details:</strong> Morris said Cousins “is the guy who is going to lead us” heading into a primetime matchup against Las Vegas next Monday, reaffirming the notion that Atlanta still isn’t considering giving rookie first-round pick Michael Penix even a spot start. Still, the Falcons now have lost four consecutive games, during which Cousins has thrown eight interceptions without a single touchdown. If Atlanta’s passing game were to notably struggle once again in Week 15, Morris’ commitment to Cousins could waver.</p> <h4 id="zay-flowers-wr">Zay Flowers (WR)</h4> <p><strong>Injury Status:</strong> Active <br/> <strong>Lineup Slot:</strong> WR <br/> <strong>Details:</strong> Flowers finished as the Ravens’ leading receiver Sunday, but both of Lamar Jackson’s passing scores went to tight ends (Mark Andrews and Isaiah Likely). The 23-year-old Flowers set a new personal best for receiving yards in a season (863) in three fewer games compared to his strong rookie campaign in 2023. The budding sophomore has become a solid option across all fantasy leagues while serving as Baltimore’s No. 1 wideout this year. The Ravens will enter a bye week before resuming play against the Giants on Dec. 15.</p> <h4 id="curtis-samuel-wr">Curtis Samuel (WR)</h4> <p><strong>Injury Status:</strong> Active <br/> <strong>Lineup Slot:</strong> BE <br/> <strong>Details:</strong> Samuel upgraded to full practice participation Friday after a pair of limited sessions, eliminating any doubt about his availability for Sunday’s matchup at SoFi Stadium. He has just 185 receiving yards and one touchdown in what has been a disappointing first season in Buffalo, and Samuel will likely see limited usage against the Rams, especially if rookie wideout Keon Coleman (questionable, wrist) suits up.</p> <h4 id="nick-chubb-rb">Nick Chubb (RB)</h4> <p><strong>Injury Status:</strong> Active <br/> <strong>Lineup Slot:</strong> BE <br/> <strong>Details:</strong> Chubb was in an even split in the backfield with Jerome Ford for the entire day. While that limited his volume, Chubb did manage a 19-yard run – his longest of the season. He’s now gained between 48 and 59 yards on the ground in four of his seven games this season, though the ongoing split in the backfield will continue to limit his fantasy appeal.</p> <h4 id="david-montgomery-rb">David Montgomery (RB)</h4> <p><strong>Injury Status:</strong> Active <br/> <strong>Lineup Slot:</strong> RB <br/> <strong>Details:</strong> Montgomery capped off the opening possession of the game with a three-yard walk-in rushing touchdown, his fifth in the last five games. The veteran back generally found running room at a premium, but he set a new season high in receptions and targets. Montgomery has consistently complemented his work on the ground with solid production through the air of late, as he’ll head into a Week 15 home showdown against the Bills on Sunday, Dec. 15 with a 14-143-0 line on 14 targets in the last four contests.</p> <h4 id="christian-watson-wr">Christian Watson (WR)</h4> <p><strong>Injury Status:</strong> Active <br/> <strong>Lineup Slot:</strong> WR <br/> <strong>Details:</strong> Watson’s night got off to an inconspicuous start when he lost a fumble after a 20-yard reception on the first play of the second quarter. While that mistake led to a Lions field goal, Watson came back to record a 59-yard catch on the Packers’ second play of the second half, and he went on to add a 29-yard grab with just under eight minutes remaining in the contest. The game marked Watson’s second over the 100-yard mark for the season, and he’s recorded at least 67 receiving yards in three of the last four contests. Watson’s production still is subject to some game-to-game volatility, but he could be in line for another robust role in a Week 15 road matchup against the Seahawks on Sunday, Dec. 15, especially if Romeo Doubs (concussion) isn’t able to make it back for that contest.</p> <h4 id="adonai-mitchell-wr">Adonai Mitchell (WR)</h4> <p><strong>Injury Status:</strong> Active <br/> <strong>Lineup Slot:</strong> BE <br/> <strong>Details:</strong> It was a disappointing performance from the rookie, who moved into a larger role with Josh Downs out due to a shoulder injury. Mitchell started opposite Michael Pittman in a two-receiver set to begin the game and played 35 of the offense’s 62 snaps while running 16 routes. Mitchell could get a chance to bounce back after Indy’s bye in Week 14, as it’s not immediately clear if Downs will be ready to return.</p> <h4 id="travis-etienne-jr-rb">Travis Etienne Jr. (RB)</h4> <p><strong>Injury Status:</strong> Active <br/> <strong>Lineup Slot:</strong> BE <br/> <strong>Details:</strong> Etienne saw his rushing role diminish significantly in Tank Bigsby’s second game back from an ankle injury, and he was out-touched 19-8. That will make Etienne tough to trust moving forward for fantasy purposes, though he did show promise as a receiver. He finished third on the team with four targets and second in yardage – highlighted by a 21-yard catch and run late in the first quarter.</p> <h4 id="xavier-worthy-wr">Xavier Worthy (WR)</h4> <p><strong>Injury Status:</strong> Active <br/> <strong>Lineup Slot:</strong> RB/WR/TE <br/> <strong>Details:</strong> Worthy made one of the game’s biggest plays down the stretch, converting on third-and-10 with a 14-yard catch to extend a drive that culminated in Matthew Wright’s game-winning 31-yard field goal. The rookie speedster has exceeded 40 receiving yards in four consecutive games after reaching that threshold only twice in his first nine appearances. Worthy will look to extend that streak in Week 15 against the Browns.</p> <h4 id="travis-kelce-te">Travis Kelce (TE)</h4> <p><strong>Injury Status:</strong> Active <br/> <strong>Lineup Slot:</strong> TE <br/> <strong>Details:</strong> Kelce became the fastest tight end in NFL history to reach 12,000 career receiving yards, doing so in his 172nd regular-season game. Tony Gonzalez had the previous record at 210 games. Kelce’s team-high 45 receiving yards included a nine-yard catch on third-and-7 coming out of the two-minute warning in the fourth quarter, which allowed Kansas City to run the clock down to one second before Matthew Wright kicked a game-winning 31-yard field goal. Heading into a Week 15 road game against the Browns, Kelce has 80 catches for 682 yards and two touchdowns this season.</p> <h4 id="alexander-mattison-rb">Alexander Mattison (RB)</h4> <p><strong>Injury Status:</strong> Questionable <br/> <strong>Lineup Slot:</strong> BE <br/> <strong>Details:</strong> questionable</p> <h4 id="gus-edwards-rb">Gus Edwards (RB)</h4> <p><strong>Injury Status:</strong> Active <br/> <strong>Lineup Slot:</strong> RB/WR/TE <br/> <strong>Details:</strong> The bruising running back scored just his second touchdown of the season. For a second consecutive week Edwards led the team in carries, but rookie Kimani Vidal was also a factor, tallying eight carries for 34 yards. The backfield breakdown is worth monitoring with J.K. Dobbins (knee) still on injured reserve for at minimum two more weeks, but it’s becoming clear Los Angeles’ rushing attack just doesn’t have the same gusto it did when Dobbins was one of the bell cows.</p> <h4 id="taysom-hill-te">Taysom Hill (TE)</h4> <p><strong>Injury Status:</strong> Injured Reserve <br/> <strong>Lineup Slot:</strong> BE <br/> <strong>Details:</strong> A torn ACL suffered Week 13 rules Hill out for the rest of the season and makes him uncertain for Week 1 of 2025. He’ll be 35 years old at that point, and it’s not entirely clear he’ll still be with the Saints. In the meantime, Juwan Johnson and Foster Moreau figure to get snaps/targets as a result of Hill’s injury.</p> <h4 id="garrett-wilson-wr">Garrett Wilson (WR)</h4> <p><strong>Injury Status:</strong> Active <br/> <strong>Lineup Slot:</strong> WR <br/> <strong>Details:</strong> Wilson beat Jalen Ramsey for a 35-yard catch on fourth down in the second quarter, and Isaiah Davis scored a 17-yard rushing touchdown on the very next play. The star wide receiver tacked on a 42-yard catch on the second play of the second half and ultimately finished with five more receiving yards than Davante Adams to lead the team. This was a welcome turnaround for Wilson, who had just 100 receiving yards over his previous three games combined. Wilson will have a nice opportunity to build on this performance in Week 15 against the beatable Jacksonville secondary.</p> <h4 id="devonta-smith-wr">DeVonta Smith (WR)</h4> <p><strong>Injury Status:</strong> Active <br/> <strong>Lineup Slot:</strong> BE <br/> <strong>Details:</strong> While his yardage was modest in his return from a two-game absence due to a hamstring strain, Smith connected with Jalen Hurts for a four-yard score just before halftime. It’s Smith’s first TD since Week 9, and he also hasn’t reached 40 receiving yards in any of his three appearances during that stretch. He’ll try to build on Sunday’s effort in Week 15 against the Steelers.</p> <h4 id="tony-pollard-rb">Tony Pollard (RB)</h4> <p><strong>Injury Status:</strong> Active <br/> <strong>Lineup Slot:</strong> RB <br/> <strong>Details:</strong> Pollard turned in a needed bounceback performance after managing only 35 yards on the ground in Week 13, and he delivered three rushes that went for a double-digit gain. He topped the century mark in rushing yards for the third time this season, all of which have come in his last six games. Pollard will remain an inconsistent option due to the poor Tennessee offense, but it’s clear that he is a driving force for the unit.</p> <h2 id="current-lineup">Current Lineup</h2> <table data-click-to-select="true" data-height="630" data-search="false" data-toggle="table" data-url="/assets/json/team_rosters/Week_14_2024_ARV_roster.json"> <thead> <tr> <th data-field="player_name" data-halign="left" data-align="left" data-sortable="true">Player</th> <th data-field="pos" data-halign="center" data-align="center" data-sortable="true">Position</th> <th data-field="slot" data-halign="center" data-align="center" data-sortable="true">Slot</th> <th data-field="points" data-halign="center" data-align="center" data-sortable="true">Points</th> <th data-field="projected" data-halign="center" data-align="center" data-sortable="true">Projected</th> </tr> </thead> </table> <p><br/><br/></p> <h2 id="optimal-lineup">Optimal Lineup</h2> <table data-click-to-select="true" data-height="630" data-search="false" data-toggle="table" data-url="/assets/json/team_rosters/Week_14_2024_ARV_optimal.json"> <thead> <tr> <th data-field="player_name" data-halign="left" data-align="left" data-sortable="true">Player</th> <th data-field="pos" data-halign="center" data-align="center" data-sortable="true">Position</th> <th data-field="slot" data-halign="center" data-align="center" data-sortable="true">Slot</th> <th data-field="points" data-halign="center" data-align="center" data-sortable="true">Points</th> <th data-field="projected" data-halign="center" data-align="center" data-sortable="true">Projected</th> </tr> </thead> </table>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="team-reports"/><category term="2024-25,"/><category term="WeeklyRecap,"/><category term="Week14"/><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Weekly team status report]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Hamlin My Business Week 14 Report</title><link href="https://family-fantasy-football.github.io/blog/2024/Week-14-HMB/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Hamlin My Business Week 14 Report"/><published>2024-12-10T22:19:38+00:00</published><updated>2024-12-10T22:19:38+00:00</updated><id>https://family-fantasy-football.github.io/blog/2024/Week-14-HMB</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://family-fantasy-football.github.io/blog/2024/Week-14-HMB/"><![CDATA[<h2 id="week-at-a-glance">Week at a Glance</h2> <p>Hamlin My Business Lost against Who Killed Charbonnet Ramsey? 144.36-168.30<br/> Current Standing: #2<br/> Playoff Chances: 100.0%<br/> Lineup Efficiency: 88.3%<br/> Best Performer: Joe Burrow (24.56 pts)<br/></p> <pre><code class="language-echarts">{
    "tooltip": {
        "trigger": "item",
        "formatter": "{a} &lt;br/&gt;{b}: {d}%"
    },
    "legend": {
        "orient": "vertical",
        "left": "left",
        "data": [
            "QB",
            "RB",
            "WR",
            "TE",
            "D/ST",
            "K"
        ]
    },
    "series": [
        {
            "name": "Position Points",
            "type": "pie",
            "radius": [
                "50%",
                "70%"
            ],
            "avoidLabelOverlap": false,
            "data": [
                {
                    "value": 46.7,
                    "name": "QB"
                },
                {
                    "value": 31.2,
                    "name": "RB"
                },
                {
                    "value": 48.4,
                    "name": "WR"
                },
                {
                    "value": 18.1,
                    "name": "TE"
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}
</code></pre> <h2 id="player-report">Player Report</h2> <h4 id="dandre-swift-rb">D’Andre Swift (RB)</h4> <p><strong>Injury Status:</strong> Active <br/> <strong>Lineup Slot:</strong> RB/WR/TE <br/> <strong>Details:</strong> Swift dealt with a quadriceps injury during the practice week before ultimately being cleared for action Sunday. The 25-year-old dominated the backfield touches, but his 15 combined touches resulted in just 40 total yards. Swift has averaged well under four yards per carry in five of his last six contests with only one trip to the end zone over that span. Things won’t get any easier for the Bears’ offense as they prepare for a road tilt against Minnesota next Monday.</p> <h4 id="joe-burrow-qb">Joe Burrow (QB)</h4> <p><strong>Injury Status:</strong> Active <br/> <strong>Lineup Slot:</strong> QB <br/> <strong>Details:</strong> Burrow was spectacular in front of a national audience Monday, but he actually came out victorious after dropping the Bengals last three games with similar performances. The soon-to-be 28-year-old only faltered on an errant pass to Ja’Marr Chase in the second half that was picked off by a Cowboys defender. Burrow now carries gaudy season totals of 3,706 passing yards to go along with 33 touchdowns (six picks) through 13 games. The fantasy stud gets a soft matchup against the Titans on Sunday for what likely will be an important playoff matchup for his managers.</p> <h4 id="devaughn-vele-wr">Devaughn Vele (WR)</h4> <p><strong>Injury Status:</strong> Active <br/> <strong>Lineup Slot:</strong> BE <br/> <strong>Details:</strong> Vele’s Week 13 performance was a major disappointment considering rookie quarterback Bo Nix threw for 294 yards against the Browns. Operating as the No. 2 wideout, Vele played 31 of the Broncos’ 66 offensive snaps Monday, second only to Courtland Sutton’s 62. The rookie will look to bounce back against the Colts on Dec. 15 when the Broncos return from their Week 14 bye.</p> <h4 id="jameson-williams-wr">Jameson Williams (WR)</h4> <p><strong>Injury Status:</strong> Active <br/> <strong>Lineup Slot:</strong> RB/WR/TE <br/> <strong>Details:</strong> Williams led the team in receiving yards on a team-high eight targets, most notably reeling in a 28-yard catch in the first quarter. The wide receiver’s dynamic skill set has led to some big performances this season, and the five catches matched his season high, which he now has accomplished in three straight games and five times overall in 2024. On the year, Williams has caught 39 of 63 targets for 710 yards and four touchdowns while appearing in 11 games.</p> <h4 id="ameer-abdullah-rb">Ameer Abdullah (RB)</h4> <p><strong>Injury Status:</strong> Active <br/> <strong>Lineup Slot:</strong> BE <br/> <strong>Details:</strong> Abdullah earned just two touches despite playing 39 percent of the Raiders’ offensive snaps, ceding much of the backfield work to Sincere McCormick as the undrafted 24-year-old took 15 carries for 78 yards to go along with a pair of receptions for another 11 yards. Abdullah figures to take a backseat to McCormick again in Week 15 when Las Vegas hosts the Falcons on Monday Night Football. Additionally, Alexander Mattison (ankle) and Zamir White (quadriceps) could return to the backfield rotation as well.</p> <h4 id="ladd-mcconkey-wr">Ladd McConkey (WR)</h4> <p><strong>Injury Status:</strong> Questionable <br/> <strong>Lineup Slot:</strong> BE <br/> <strong>Details:</strong> questionable</p> <h4 id="demarcus-robinson-wr">Demarcus Robinson (WR)</h4> <p><strong>Injury Status:</strong> Questionable <br/> <strong>Lineup Slot:</strong> BE <br/> <strong>Details:</strong> Robinson missed much of the third quarter Sunday against the Bills due to a shoulder injury but was able to return to action. On Monday, coach Sean McVay clarified the nature of Robinson’s health concern, calling it an AC joint sprain, per Adam Grosbard of The Orange County Register. With a DNP to kick off Week 15 prep, Robinson now will have a maximum of two chances to prove his health ahead of Thursday’s game at San Francisco.</p> <h4 id="matthew-stafford-qb">Matthew Stafford (QB)</h4> <p><strong>Injury Status:</strong> Active <br/> <strong>Lineup Slot:</strong> BE <br/> <strong>Details:</strong> Despite the score and the stat line of Josh Allen, the Rams prioritized their running game. That limited Stafford’s passing volume, but he made up for that by averaging 10.7 yards per attempt while completing four passes of more than 20 yards. He also found the end zone on passes of 17 and 19 yards to Puka Nacua and Cooper Kupp, respectively. Stafford now has multiple scores in four straight games with no interceptions, though this was his first 300-yard performance since Week 1.</p> <h4 id="tyreek-hill-wr">Tyreek Hill (WR)</h4> <p><strong>Injury Status:</strong> Active <br/> <strong>Lineup Slot:</strong> WR <br/> <strong>Details:</strong> Hill and Jaylen Waddle posted identical first-half stat lines of five catches for 61 yards, and they ultimately accounted for 214 of Tua Tagovailoa’s 331 passing yards as the Dolphins capitalized on the absence of star Jets cornerback Sauce Gardner (hamstring). Hill’s four-yard touchdown catch followed by a two-point conversion to Waddle helped Miami tie the game 23-23 with 9:04 to play in regulation. Despite playing through a wrist injury in recent weeks, Hill has been heating up. The speedster has scored in four of the past five games, and Hill has topped 80 receiving yards in each of his last two outings ahead of a Week 15 road game against the Texans after reaching that mark only twice through Week 12.</p> <h4 id="aaron-jones-rb">Aaron Jones (RB)</h4> <p><strong>Injury Status:</strong> Active <br/> <strong>Lineup Slot:</strong> RB <br/> <strong>Details:</strong> A week after having issues with ball security, Jones turned in a clean performance that also featured his third performance of better than 70 rushing yards in the last five contests. Jones also recorded his second rushing touchdown in the last three games on a 15-yard run with 3:38 remaining to cap off the runaway win. The veteran back heads into a Week 15 home matchup against the Bears on Monday night, Dec. 16 now just 117 rushing yards away from the fourth 1,000-yard campaign of his career.</p> <h4 id="hunter-henry-te">Hunter Henry (TE)</h4> <p><strong>Injury Status:</strong> Active <br/> <strong>Lineup Slot:</strong> BE <br/> <strong>Details:</strong> The veteran tight end once again led the Patriots in catches, targets and receiving yards, but Henry got denied a bigger performance when Austin Hooper caught Drake Maye’s only TD of the day in the second quarter instead. Henry is on the verge of a career-best campaign, needing just three more catches and 43 more yards to set new personal bests in those categories. He’ll aim for those marks on the other side of New England’s Week 14 bye.</p> <h4 id="marquez-valdes-scantling-wr">Marquez Valdes-Scantling (WR)</h4> <p><strong>Injury Status:</strong> Active <br/> <strong>Lineup Slot:</strong> BE <br/> <strong>Details:</strong> The veteran wideout led the Saints in receiving yards, just nudging out Juwan Johnson’s 50, but it was the tight end who caught Derek Carr’s only TD. The QB left the game late in the fourth quarter to be checked out for a concussion and a hand injury, and while Valdes-Scantling has an 11-283-4 line on 17 targets over the last four games, he’ll likely have trouble finding the same success in Week 15 against the Commanders if Jake Haener or Spencer Rattler is under center for the Saints instead of Carr.</p> <h4 id="malik-nabers-wr">Malik Nabers (WR)</h4> <p><strong>Injury Status:</strong> Active <br/> <strong>Lineup Slot:</strong> WR <br/> <strong>Details:</strong> While it wasn’t an efficient performance, Nabers led the Giants in receiving yards and tied for the team lead in catches with Tyrone Tracy and Daniel Bellinger. Nabers hasn’t gotten into the end zone since Week 3, but the rookie wideout has caught at least five passes in six straight games despite the team’s QB turmoil, posting a 41-392-0 line on 66 targets. Nabers will try to take advantage of an exploitable secondary in Week 15 against the Ravens.</p> <h4 id="najee-harris-rb">Najee Harris (RB)</h4> <p><strong>Injury Status:</strong> Active <br/> <strong>Lineup Slot:</strong> RB <br/> <strong>Details:</strong> The Steelers had a mediocre day offensively, with nearly all of their skill-position players posting modest stat lines. Harris was no exception, as he managed only 3.3 yards per carry despite tallying a 20-yard gain for the second consecutive game. Even with the inefficiency, Harris still managed a decent fantasy performance thanks to a one-yard touchdown run early in the second quarter. Since Russell Wilson has taken over under center, Harris has four trips to the end zone in seven contests, though he’s failed to reach 80 yards on the ground in five straight matchups.</p> <h4 id="george-kittle-te">George Kittle (TE)</h4> <p><strong>Injury Status:</strong> Active <br/> <strong>Lineup Slot:</strong> TE <br/> <strong>Details:</strong> Kittle played like a man possessed against the Bears after recording just one reception for seven yards the week prior. Weather played a huge role in the road stinker against Buffalo, so Sunday’s sunny conditions allowed the star tight end to feast on Chicago’s defense. Kittle upped his season line to 56-800-8 in the much-needed win, confirming the tight end’s upper-echelon status in fantasy ahead of Thursday’s primetime tilt against the Rams.</p> <h4 id="brock-purdy-qb">Brock Purdy (QB)</h4> <p><strong>Injury Status:</strong> Active <br/> <strong>Lineup Slot:</strong> OP <br/> <strong>Details:</strong> Purdy did suffer an injury scare in the fourth quarter on a roughing the passer penalty that saw the quarterback’s body bend backward in an awkward fashion between two Chicago defenders. The star QB was writhing in pain on the ground following the hit, but he wound up missing just one play before returning to the field, as reported by 49ers’ reporter Cam Inman. Aside from the brief injury scare, Purdy was firing on all cylinders against the scuttling Bears, which comes as a relief to fantasy managers following last week’s dud against the Bills in the snow. Assuming that there are no lingering effects from getting clotheslined Sunday, Purdy could be in store for another high score in a potential shootout against the Rams on Thursday Night Football in Week 15.</p> <h4 id="nick-westbrook-ikhine-wr">Nick Westbrook-Ikhine (WR)</h4> <p><strong>Injury Status:</strong> Active <br/> <strong>Lineup Slot:</strong> WR <br/> <strong>Details:</strong> Westbrook-Ikhine has been reliant upon big plays all season, though he had been carving out a bigger role in the Tennessee offense by commanding at least five targets in three straight games. He took a step back in Sunday’s loss, drawing his lowest target count since Week 6. Westbrook-Ikhine should have the chance to rebound in Week 15 against the Bengals, though the state of the Titans’ offense will leave him as a boom-or-bust option down the stretch.</p> <h2 id="current-lineup">Current Lineup</h2> <table data-click-to-select="true" data-height="630" data-search="false" data-toggle="table" data-url="/assets/json/team_rosters/Week_14_2024_HMB_roster.json"> <thead> <tr> <th data-field="player_name" data-halign="left" data-align="left" data-sortable="true">Player</th> <th data-field="pos" data-halign="center" data-align="center" data-sortable="true">Position</th> <th data-field="slot" data-halign="center" data-align="center" data-sortable="true">Slot</th> <th data-field="points" data-halign="center" data-align="center" data-sortable="true">Points</th> <th data-field="projected" data-halign="center" data-align="center" data-sortable="true">Projected</th> </tr> </thead> </table> <p><br/><br/></p> <h2 id="optimal-lineup">Optimal Lineup</h2> <table data-click-to-select="true" data-height="630" data-search="false" data-toggle="table" data-url="/assets/json/team_rosters/Week_14_2024_HMB_optimal.json"> <thead> <tr> <th data-field="player_name" data-halign="left" data-align="left" data-sortable="true">Player</th> <th data-field="pos" data-halign="center" data-align="center" data-sortable="true">Position</th> <th data-field="slot" data-halign="center" data-align="center" data-sortable="true">Slot</th> <th data-field="points" data-halign="center" data-align="center" data-sortable="true">Points</th> <th data-field="projected" data-halign="center" data-align="center" data-sortable="true">Projected</th> </tr> </thead> </table>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="team-reports"/><category term="2024-25,"/><category term="WeeklyRecap,"/><category term="Week14"/><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Weekly team status report]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Mama Daughter Duo Week 14 Report</title><link href="https://family-fantasy-football.github.io/blog/2024/Week-14-JST/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Mama Daughter Duo Week 14 Report"/><published>2024-12-10T22:19:38+00:00</published><updated>2024-12-10T22:19:38+00:00</updated><id>https://family-fantasy-football.github.io/blog/2024/Week-14-JST</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://family-fantasy-football.github.io/blog/2024/Week-14-JST/"><![CDATA[<h2 id="week-at-a-glance">Week at a Glance</h2> <p>Mama Daughter Duo Won against Abbey Road to Victory 131.46-108.02<br/> Current Standing: #7<br/> Playoff Chances: 0.0%<br/> Lineup Efficiency: 83.5%<br/> Best Performer: Jordan Addison (35.30 pts)<br/></p> <pre><code class="language-echarts">{
    "tooltip": {
        "trigger": "item",
        "formatter": "{a} &lt;br/&gt;{b}: {d}%"
    },
    "legend": {
        "orient": "vertical",
        "left": "left",
        "data": [
            "QB",
            "RB",
            "WR",
            "TE",
            "D/ST",
            "K"
        ]
    },
    "series": [
        {
            "name": "Position Points",
            "type": "pie",
            "radius": [
                "50%",
                "70%"
            ],
            "avoidLabelOverlap": false,
            "data": [
                {
                    "value": 12.0,
                    "name": "QB"
                },
                {
                    "value": 49.7,
                    "name": "RB"
                },
                {
                    "value": 56.1,
                    "name": "WR"
                },
                {
                    "value": 13.7,
                    "name": "TE"
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}
</code></pre> <h2 id="player-report">Player Report</h2> <h4 id="chuba-hubbard-rb">Chuba Hubbard (RB)</h4> <p><strong>Injury Status:</strong> Active <br/> <strong>Lineup Slot:</strong> RB <br/> <strong>Details:</strong> Hubbard has established himself as the clear No. 1 option leading the Panthers’ rushing attack this season, and he rushed 26 times for 92 yards and one touchdown versus Philadelphia, but there had been an assumption that Brooks’ involvement would ramp up down the stretch. With the rookie second-round pick having re-torn his right ACL, though, Carolina’s roster no longer features anyone even resembling a threat to Hubbard’s dominant share of reps. Raheem Blackshear (chest) is considered day-to-day, while veteran Miles Sanders (ankle) won’t be eligible to come off IR until Week 16 against Arizona, at the earliest. Head coach Dave Canales said practice-squad player Mike Boone currently is in line to handle the No. 2 role behind Hubbard at practice and potentially Week 15 versus Dallas, per Steve Reed of the Associated Press.</p> <h4 id="keenan-allen-wr">Keenan Allen (WR)</h4> <p><strong>Injury Status:</strong> Active <br/> <strong>Lineup Slot:</strong> BE <br/> <strong>Details:</strong> Allen overcame a minor ankle injury during the practice week in order to suit up for Sunday’s eventual loss. The seasoned veteran posted vanilla numbers on the heels of his two most-productive games. Allen has underwhelmed in Chicago outside of the two aforementioned performances, averaging just 3.7 receptions and 34.7 yards in nine other games this season. Perhaps the 32-year-old has finally lost a step in his 12th year, or his down numbers could simply be the result of the Bears’ overall ineptitude on offense. Whatever the case, Allen checks in as a middling fantasy option ahead of next Monday’s road tilt against the Vikings.</p> <h4 id="david-njoku-te">David Njoku (TE)</h4> <p><strong>Injury Status:</strong> Active <br/> <strong>Lineup Slot:</strong> TE <br/> <strong>Details:</strong> Njoku led the Browns in targets and receptions, though he was held to short yardage for much of the game. He broke that trend with a leaping 15-yard touchdown grab midway through the fourth quarter, and he now has three touchdowns across his last two games. Njoku has also emerged as a clear favorite target of Jameis Winston, combining to command 30 targets in that same two-contest span while seeing at least nine opportunities in three of his last four contests.</p> <h4 id="brandin-cooks-wr">Brandin Cooks (WR)</h4> <p><strong>Injury Status:</strong> Active <br/> <strong>Lineup Slot:</strong> BE <br/> <strong>Details:</strong> Cooks’ limitations in Thursday’s practice were primarily rest-related as he gets eased back in ahead of his second game back from a two-month absence due to a knee injury. Barring a setback Saturday, the veteran wideout should head into Monday’s matchup with the struggling Bengals secondary sans an injury designation.</p> <h4 id="courtland-sutton-wr">Courtland Sutton (WR)</h4> <p><strong>Injury Status:</strong> Active <br/> <strong>Lineup Slot:</strong> RB/WR/TE <br/> <strong>Details:</strong> Sutton led the Broncos in both targets and receptions Monday, but he was second to Marvin Mims after the latter broke off a 93-yard touchdown in the high-scoring affair. The 29-year-old Sutton has posted three 100-plus-yard performances over the last six weeks, chipping in three touchdowns over that span as well. With Denver entering a bye week, Sutton will have to wait until Sunday, Dec. 15 against Indianapolis in order to continue his current tear.</p> <h4 id="bo-nix-qb">Bo Nix (QB)</h4> <p><strong>Injury Status:</strong> Active <br/> <strong>Lineup Slot:</strong> QB <br/> <strong>Details:</strong> Nix turned in mixed results in Monday’s thrilling victory, throwing his 17th touchdown in addition to his seventh and eighth interceptions of the season. The rookie standout didn’t have his best game as a rusher, either, but his 294 passing yards was his second-highest total through 13 starts. Nix has been progressing well since enduring a slow start to the campaign, making him a viable fantasy option coming out of the upcoming bye against the Colts on Sunday, Dec. 15.</p> <h4 id="jayden-reed-wr">Jayden Reed (WR)</h4> <p><strong>Injury Status:</strong> Active <br/> <strong>Lineup Slot:</strong> BE <br/> <strong>Details:</strong> Reed played 50 percent of snaps, which ties for his lowest share this season but doesn’t fall outside the normal range. It’s the seventh time he’s logged 50-59 percent of snaps, as he still doesn’t get much playing time in formations with fewer than three wide receivers. Reed has just one game all year with more than six targets, making him highly dependent on touchdowns and big plays, especially relative to other WRs that primarily man the slot. He has 12 targets and 73 receiving yards over the past four games, but with three of his eight catches in that span going for touchdowns. Reed will be a high-risk, high-reward lineup option once again Week 15 at Seattle, facing a defense that often uses top cornerback Devon Witherspoon in the slot.</p> <h4 id="anthony-richardson-qb">Anthony Richardson (QB)</h4> <p><strong>Injury Status:</strong> Active <br/> <strong>Lineup Slot:</strong> OP <br/> <strong>Details:</strong> That two-point conversion came with 12 seconds left in the fourth quarter, after Richardson had led a five-minute scoring drive that he capped with a three-yard TD pass to Alec Pierce on fourth down. A poor completion rate is simply part of the package with the second-year QB at this stage of his development, but there’s no denying Richardson’s athletic upside, and since reclaiming the starting job for the Colts he’s produced six touchdowns (three passing, three rushing) in three games. The Colts are on bye in Week 14, giving Richardson time to recharge ahead of the team’s final push for the playoffs.</p> <h4 id="isiah-pacheco-rb">Isiah Pacheco (RB)</h4> <p><strong>Injury Status:</strong> Active <br/> <strong>Lineup Slot:</strong> RB <br/> <strong>Details:</strong> Pacheco returned to the clear-cut lead role in his second game back from a fractured fibula, as Kareem Hunt and Samaje Perine combined for just eight touches. After posting 189 scrimmage yards and a touchdown in two games prior to the injury, Pacheco has 110 total yards without a score in two games since returning. Pacheco will look to pick up the pace in Week 15 against the Browns.</p> <h4 id="tre-tucker-wr">Tre Tucker (WR)</h4> <p><strong>Injury Status:</strong> Active <br/> <strong>Lineup Slot:</strong> BE <br/> <strong>Details:</strong> Tucker was one of four Raiders pass catchers to earn at least five targets Sunday, but he was by far the least productive with his looks, producing only seven yards on two receptions. The speedster remains a boom-or-bust option in Week 15 against a Falcons secondary that just allowed Vikings wideouts Justin Jefferson and Jordan Addison to combine for a 15-265-5 receiving line on 19 targets, though Tucker may be catching passes from quarterback Desmond Ridder after Aidan O’Connell suffered a bone bruise to his left leg Sunday.</p> <h4 id="jordan-addison-wr">Jordan Addison (WR)</h4> <p><strong>Injury Status:</strong> Active <br/> <strong>Lineup Slot:</strong> WR <br/> <strong>Details:</strong> Addison led the Vikings across the board in receptions, receiving yards and targets, narrowly edging Justin Jefferson by one in the first two categories. The second-year wideout’s season had been considered largely disappointing until three games ago, when Addison turned in an 8-162-1 line against the Bears at Soldier Field. Sunday’s performance saw Addison establish a new single-game career high in touchdown catches with scoring receptions of 49, 11 and six yards, and it also featured a season-high-tying reception tally and a new high-water mark in targets. Given his recent body of work, Addison will head into a Week 15 divisional showdown against the Bears on Monday night, Dec. 16 with plenty of momentum.</p> <h4 id="derek-carr-qb">Derek Carr (QB)</h4> <p><strong>Injury Status:</strong> Questionable <br/> <strong>Lineup Slot:</strong> BE <br/> <strong>Details:</strong> Rizzi noted the fracture to Carr’s left, non-throwing hand currently doesn’t appear as though it will require surgery, Ross Jackson of WWL Louisiana reports. The interim head coach also said it’s possible that Carr could start Sunday’s game against the Commanders even if he’s unable to practice this week, per Sean Fazende of Fox 8 New Orleans. It would be a tall task, though, for the veteran signal-caller to both clear the five-step concussion protocol fully and reach a level of comfort with his injured hand to handle full contact and play Week 15. If Carr isn’t able to suit up versus Washington, starting duties will fall to one of Jake Haener or Spencer Rattler.</p> <h4 id="pat-freiermuth-te">Pat Freiermuth (TE)</h4> <p><strong>Injury Status:</strong> Active <br/> <strong>Lineup Slot:</strong> BE <br/> <strong>Details:</strong> Russell Wilson took to the air only 26 times, leading to limited volume for all of Pittsburgh’s pass catchers. Freiermuth made the most of his chances, highlighted by long gains of 21 and 20 yards – the latter of which went for a touchdown. He has now found the end zone in three of his last five games and has at least 45 receiving yards in three straight contests after reaching that mark just once in his first 10 matchups.</p> <h4 id="dk-metcalf-wr">DK Metcalf (WR)</h4> <p><strong>Injury Status:</strong> Active <br/> <strong>Lineup Slot:</strong> WR <br/> <strong>Details:</strong> Metcalf finished second in targets behind running back Zach Charbonnet (seven) while checking in third in receiving yards behind Charbonnet and fellow wideout Jaxon Smith-Njigba. The 27-year-old Metcalf’s modest production out of the team’s Week 10 bye may have fantasy managers concerned, but the wideout has maintained a high floor of 4.8 receptions and 61.0 yards during the mild four-game cold spell. Keep faith in Metcalf, as the Seahawks may require more from their receivers at home against Green Bay next Sunday.</p> <h4 id="zach-charbonnet-rb">Zach Charbonnet (RB)</h4> <p><strong>Injury Status:</strong> Active <br/> <strong>Lineup Slot:</strong> BE <br/> <strong>Details:</strong> Starter Kenneth Walker (ankle/calf) was unable to suit up for Sunday’s crucial NFC West battle, opening the door for Charbonnet to make his third start of the campaign. The sophomore backup wound up setting new career highs in both rushing (134) and receiving yards (59) while punching in a pair of touchdowns. Five of Charbonnet’s seven touchdown rushes have come in three spot-starts for Walker this season, highlighting the major fantasy value that can be unearthed in those scenarios. Fantasy managers who missed out on Sunday’s point bonanza should monitor Walker’s status for Week 15 before putting in large bids for Seattle’s talented backup ahead of next Sunday’s tilt against Green Bay.</p> <h4 id="rachaad-white-rb">Rachaad White (RB)</h4> <p><strong>Injury Status:</strong> Active <br/> <strong>Lineup Slot:</strong> RB/WR/TE <br/> <strong>Details:</strong> White’s backfield mate Bucky Irving exited the game for good in the first half with a back injury, and White was able to take advantage with a season-high rushing yardage total. The game marked the third-year pro’s second straight efficient effort, as he’d also recorded 76 yards on 11 carries, albeit with the help of a big run in overtime, in a Week 13 win over the Panthers. White added his third rushing touchdown of the season on a three-yard run in the fourth quarter, a score preceded by a five-yard TD grab in the opening period. White’s fantasy prospects are on an upswing irrespective of Irving’s status going into a Week 15 road matchup against the Chargers.</p> <h4 id="calvin-ridley-wr">Calvin Ridley (WR)</h4> <p><strong>Injury Status:</strong> Active <br/> <strong>Lineup Slot:</strong> WR <br/> <strong>Details:</strong> Ridley dominated opportunity in the passing game, as no other Titans pass catcher saw more than four targets. That didn’t lead to a great stat line, and Ridley ultimately needed a long 30-yard reception midway through the fourth quarter to have even a mediocre performance. He also drew negative attention for stepping out of bounds on a third-down play while seemingly having the chance to turn upfield to get past the sticks. The Titans failed to convert on the next play, ending Tennessee’s best chance to win the game. Ridley has been held below 60 receiving yards in three of his last four matchups.</p> <h2 id="current-lineup">Current Lineup</h2> <table data-click-to-select="true" data-height="630" data-search="false" data-toggle="table" data-url="/assets/json/team_rosters/Week_14_2024_JST_roster.json"> <thead> <tr> <th data-field="player_name" data-halign="left" data-align="left" data-sortable="true">Player</th> <th data-field="pos" data-halign="center" data-align="center" data-sortable="true">Position</th> <th data-field="slot" data-halign="center" data-align="center" data-sortable="true">Slot</th> <th data-field="points" data-halign="center" data-align="center" data-sortable="true">Points</th> <th data-field="projected" data-halign="center" data-align="center" data-sortable="true">Projected</th> </tr> </thead> </table> <p><br/><br/></p> <h2 id="optimal-lineup">Optimal Lineup</h2> <table data-click-to-select="true" data-height="630" data-search="false" data-toggle="table" data-url="/assets/json/team_rosters/Week_14_2024_JST_optimal.json"> <thead> <tr> <th data-field="player_name" data-halign="left" data-align="left" data-sortable="true">Player</th> <th data-field="pos" data-halign="center" data-align="center" data-sortable="true">Position</th> <th data-field="slot" data-halign="center" data-align="center" data-sortable="true">Slot</th> <th data-field="points" data-halign="center" data-align="center" data-sortable="true">Points</th> <th data-field="projected" data-halign="center" data-align="center" data-sortable="true">Projected</th> </tr> </thead> </table>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="team-reports"/><category term="2024-25,"/><category term="WeeklyRecap,"/><category term="Week14"/><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Weekly team status report]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Fantasy Guru Kayden Week 14 Report</title><link href="https://family-fantasy-football.github.io/blog/2024/Week-14-KTT/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Fantasy Guru Kayden Week 14 Report"/><published>2024-12-10T22:19:38+00:00</published><updated>2024-12-10T22:19:38+00:00</updated><id>https://family-fantasy-football.github.io/blog/2024/Week-14-KTT</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://family-fantasy-football.github.io/blog/2024/Week-14-KTT/"><![CDATA[<h2 id="week-at-a-glance">Week at a Glance</h2> <p>Fantasy Guru Kayden Won against Michael’s Managable Team 123.40-72.52<br/> Current Standing: #10<br/> Playoff Chances: 0.0%<br/> Lineup Efficiency: 89.0%<br/> Best Performer: Josh Allen (51.88 pts)<br/></p> <pre><code class="language-echarts">{
    "tooltip": {
        "trigger": "item",
        "formatter": "{a} &lt;br/&gt;{b}: {d}%"
    },
    "legend": {
        "orient": "vertical",
        "left": "left",
        "data": [
            "QB",
            "RB",
            "WR",
            "TE",
            "D/ST",
            "K"
        ]
    },
    "series": [
        {
            "name": "Position Points",
            "type": "pie",
            "radius": [
                "50%",
                "70%"
            ],
            "avoidLabelOverlap": false,
            "data": [
                {
                    "value": 58.9,
                    "name": "QB"
                },
                {
                    "value": 5.7,
                    "name": "RB"
                },
                {
                    "value": 52.3,
                    "name": "WR"
                },
                {
                    "value": 6.5,
                    "name": "TE"
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}
</code></pre> <h2 id="player-report">Player Report</h2> <h4 id="kyle-pitts-te">Kyle Pitts (TE)</h4> <p><strong>Injury Status:</strong> Active <br/> <strong>Lineup Slot:</strong> BE <br/> <strong>Details:</strong> Pitts was a respectable play during the first half of the season, posting 34 receptions (on 49 targets) for 485 yards and three touchdowns across his first 10 appearances. However, over the past four games, Pitts has two receptions (on 11 targets) for 23 yards. During that stretch, QB Kirk Cousins had some solid yardage totals, but he threw eight INTs and zero TDs. Despite that horrid stretch, the Falcons aren’t planning on making a change at QB, even though rookie Michael Penix has looked good in limited action.</p> <h4 id="drake-london-wr">Drake London (WR)</h4> <p><strong>Injury Status:</strong> Active <br/> <strong>Lineup Slot:</strong> RB/WR/TE <br/> <strong>Details:</strong> London had a solid but relatively unspectacular afternoon despite Kirk Cousins’ 344-yard tally, finishing third in receiving yards behind Darnell Mooney and the surging Ray-Ray McCloud. The third-year wideout did finish second in targets, and he’s now reached at least 70 receiving yards in three of the past four games while notching double-digit targets in each of those contests. London next takes aim at a vulnerable Raiders defense in a Week 15 road matchup on Monday night, Dec. 16.</p> <h4 id="josh-allen-qb">Josh Allen (QB)</h4> <p><strong>Injury Status:</strong> Active <br/> <strong>Lineup Slot:</strong> QB <br/> <strong>Details:</strong> Allen had a prolific performance in the loss, accounting for all six of Buffalo’s touchdowns on the day – a pair of which came on 51- and 41-yard touchdown throws. He also completed a total of six passes that went for more than 20 yards, leading to his highest yardage total of the campaign and his second performance of more than 300 yards. Allen supplemented his work through the air by getting more aggressive with his legs, as his 82 yards on the ground were a season high. He also has at least one rushing score in four straight contests. All told, Allen became the first NFL player to account for three passing and three rushing touchdowns in a regular-season game in NFL history, per NFL.com.</p> <h4 id="trey-sermon-rb">Trey Sermon (RB)</h4> <p><strong>Injury Status:</strong> Active <br/> <strong>Lineup Slot:</strong> BE <br/> <strong>Details:</strong> Sermon continues to see little opportunity in a backfield dominated by Jonathan Taylor. The Ohio State product hasn’t had a carry since Week 9, or a target in either of the team’s last two contests. However, he was involved in the return game and had a 23-yard kick return Sunday. Indianapolis has a Week 14 bye, but Sermon will be back on the field in Week 15 against Denver and likely continue seeing limited opportunities unless Taylor suffers an injury.</p> <h4 id="jonathan-taylor-rb">Jonathan Taylor (RB)</h4> <p><strong>Injury Status:</strong> Active <br/> <strong>Lineup Slot:</strong> BE <br/> <strong>Details:</strong> The veteran RB just missed compiling 100 rushing yards for the fifth time in 10 appearances this season, and Taylor ended his four-game scoring drought with his first TD reception of the year late in the first quarter. Taylor heads into the Colts’ Week 14 bye only 78 yards short of 1,000 scrimmage yards, a mark he reached in each of his first three NFL seasons before falling short in an injury-plagued 2023.</p> <h4 id="kareem-hunt-rb">Kareem Hunt (RB)</h4> <p><strong>Injury Status:</strong> Active <br/> <strong>Lineup Slot:</strong> RB <br/> <strong>Details:</strong> Hunt has seen a nosedive in his playing time over the last couple weeks, claiming just 20 snaps (29 percent of team snaps) in Week 14 compared to north of 50 percent when he was serving in the starting role. He’s also seen just a combined 15 touches over the last two games after averaging 19.4 carries and 2.1 catches from Weeks 4-12, a massive downgrade in his workload. Hunt should continue to operate as the Chiefs’ RB2 behind Isiah Pacheco, but he’s a clear second on the depth chart at this juncture with a significantly lower fantasy ceiling than he previously sported as a starter.</p> <h4 id="deandre-hopkins-wr">DeAndre Hopkins (WR)</h4> <p><strong>Injury Status:</strong> Active <br/> <strong>Lineup Slot:</strong> RB/WR/TE <br/> <strong>Details:</strong> Hopkins scored a nine-yard touchdown in the second quarter and got both hands on a deep ball just outside the end zone early in the fourth before having it knocked out by a jarring hit for an incomplete pass. He accounted for Kansas City’s only touchdown of the game but finished third on the team in receiving yards behind Travis Kelce (45) and Xavier Worthy (41) despite pacing the team in targets. Hopkins has established himself as the No. 1 wide receiver in Kansas City heading into a Week 15 matchup with the Browns, notching nine targets in three of his last six games while scoring four touchdowns over that span.</p> <h4 id="zamir-white-rb">Zamir White (RB)</h4> <p><strong>Injury Status:</strong> Injured Reserve <br/> <strong>Lineup Slot:</strong> BE <br/> <strong>Details:</strong> White’s placement on IR rules him out for Las Vegas’ final four games of the regular season, ending his 2024 campaign. The 2022 fourth-round pick had already missed the Raiders’ last three games due to a quad injury. Despite entering the season with significant opportunity, White’s Year 3 season resolves as one to forget. Across eight appearances, White rushed 65 times for just 183 yards (2.8 YPC) and one touchdown, while also securing six of eight targets for 30 yards. Alexander Mattison (ankle) and Sincere McCormick remain available atop Las Vegas’ depth chart.</p> <h4 id="jakobi-meyers-wr">Jakobi Meyers (WR)</h4> <p><strong>Injury Status:</strong> Active <br/> <strong>Lineup Slot:</strong> WR <br/> <strong>Details:</strong> Despite the disappointing team outcome and Aidan O’Connell’s exit in the second half due to a knee injury, the ever-reliable Meyers turned in another productive effort that included a co-team-high reception total. The veteran wideout also set the pace in targets and finished just a yard short of drawing even with Michael Mayer for the team lead in receiving yards. Meyers has at least six catches in five of the last six contests heading into a Week 15 Monday night home matchup against the Falcons on Dec. 16.</p> <h4 id="tj-hockenson-te">T.J. Hockenson (TE)</h4> <p><strong>Injury Status:</strong> Active <br/> <strong>Lineup Slot:</strong> TE <br/> <strong>Details:</strong> The veteran tight end was quiet throughout most of the afternoon, but he opened the second half with catches of 10 and 18 yards on the Vikings’ first possession of the third quarter. Hockenson’s reception total was the third highest of his injury-delayed season, as was his yardage tally. Hockenson and the Vikings next welcome in the Bears for a Week 15 home matchup on Monday night, Dec. 16.</p> <h4 id="davante-adams-wr">Davante Adams (WR)</h4> <p><strong>Injury Status:</strong> Active <br/> <strong>Lineup Slot:</strong> WR <br/> <strong>Details:</strong> After a quiet start, Adams came alive with four catches for 54 yards – including a 34-yard reception – on the Jets’ final drive of the first half, which resulted in a go-ahead field goal. Adams kept rolling to begin the second half, catching a three-yard touchdown pass to restore the lead. Miami ultimately came back to tie the game in the final seconds of regulation and won it in overtime without giving the Jets a chance to possess the ball, but Adams still managed to post his highest yardage total as a member of the Jets. Adams has notched at least 11 targets in four of his past five games, so he’s likely to play a significant role once again in Week 15 against a weak Jacksonville pass defense.</p> <h4 id="george-pickens-wr">George Pickens (WR)</h4> <p><strong>Injury Status:</strong> Questionable <br/> <strong>Lineup Slot:</strong> WR <br/> <strong>Details:</strong> Though Pickens was listed as questionable leading up to this past Sunday’s game against the Browns, reports heading into the day suggested that the wideout was likely to play. However, a pregame workout apparently didn’t go as well as anticipated, and Pickens ended up sitting out the Steelers’ 27-14 victory. The Steelers aren’t yet ruling Pickens out for Week 15, but he looks as though he’ll face an uphill battle to improve enough in his recovery from a Grade 2 hamstring strain to give it a go this Sunday. Assuming Pickens remains out for a second straight game, Van Jefferson, Calvin Austin, Mike Williams, Scotty Miller and Ben Skowronek could all benefit from expanded roles as the Steelers’ available options at receiver, while tight end Pat Freiermuth (3-48-1 receiving line on three targets in Week 14) could see more involvement in the passing attack.</p> <h4 id="sterling-shepard-wr">Sterling Shepard (WR)</h4> <p><strong>Injury Status:</strong> Active <br/> <strong>Lineup Slot:</strong> BE <br/> <strong>Details:</strong> Shepard put together another solid performance as the Buccaneers’ third receiver, tying starters Mike Evans and Jalen McMillan for the team lead in receptions while checking in third in receiving yards with a figure that also qualified as a new season high. Shepard has experienced somewhat of a resurgence playing with college teammate Baker Mayfield following a forgettable and injury-plagued final three seasons with the Giants, posting a 29-287-1 line on 45 targets over 11 games, including at least four receptions in four of the last five contests.</p> <h4 id="bucky-irving-rb">Bucky Irving (RB)</h4> <p><strong>Injury Status:</strong> Questionable <br/> <strong>Lineup Slot:</strong> RB <br/> <strong>Details:</strong> Bowles said Irving’s availability Week 15 against the Chargers will depend on whether his back loosens up in time for the road matchup. In the event that Irving isn’t able to get right in time to suit up in Los Angeles, Rachaad White will be positioned to lead Tampa Bay’s backfield, with Sean Tucker handling the No. 2 role.</p> <h4 id="will-levis-qb">Will Levis (QB)</h4> <p><strong>Injury Status:</strong> Questionable <br/> <strong>Lineup Slot:</strong> OP <br/> <strong>Details:</strong> Levis drew one of the best matchups in the league against a struggling Jaguars defense, but he managed to do little with the opportunity. Tennessee didn’t find the end zone on the day, while Levis averaged only 5.3 yards per attempt. Most concerning was that he aggravated the AC joint sprain that cost him three games earlier in the season on a hard hit on the final play of the first half, per Turron Davenport of ESPN.com. That likely affected his performance in the final two quarters of the loss and casts doubt on his status moving forward.</p> <h4 id="zach-ertz-te">Zach Ertz (TE)</h4> <p><strong>Injury Status:</strong> Active <br/> <strong>Lineup Slot:</strong> BE <br/> <strong>Details:</strong> Ertz extended Washington’s lead to 35-13 with a four-yard touchdown catch in the fourth quarter. He has scored in three consecutive games after recording only one touchdown through 10 games with the Commanders. Ertz will look to extend his touchdown streak in Week 15 against the Saints after a Week 14 bye.</p> <h4 id="brian-robinson-jr-rb">Brian Robinson Jr. (RB)</h4> <p><strong>Injury Status:</strong> Active <br/> <strong>Lineup Slot:</strong> BE <br/> <strong>Details:</strong> Robinson quickly showed that he’s over the ankle injury he sustained in the Week 12 loss to Dallas, opening the scoring with a 40-yard touchdown run on the game’s first possession. That hot start helped Robinson post his third 100-yard rushing performance of the season and first since Week 4. With Austin Ekeler (concussion) on IR, Robinson should continue to handle heavy workloads as the clear lead back after Washington’s Week 14 bye.</p> <h2 id="current-lineup">Current Lineup</h2> <table data-click-to-select="true" data-height="630" data-search="false" data-toggle="table" data-url="/assets/json/team_rosters/Week_14_2024_KTT_roster.json"> <thead> <tr> <th data-field="player_name" data-halign="left" data-align="left" data-sortable="true">Player</th> <th data-field="pos" data-halign="center" data-align="center" data-sortable="true">Position</th> <th data-field="slot" data-halign="center" data-align="center" data-sortable="true">Slot</th> <th data-field="points" data-halign="center" data-align="center" data-sortable="true">Points</th> <th data-field="projected" data-halign="center" data-align="center" data-sortable="true">Projected</th> </tr> </thead> </table> <p><br/><br/></p> <h2 id="optimal-lineup">Optimal Lineup</h2> <table data-click-to-select="true" data-height="630" data-search="false" data-toggle="table" data-url="/assets/json/team_rosters/Week_14_2024_KTT_optimal.json"> <thead> <tr> <th data-field="player_name" data-halign="left" data-align="left" data-sortable="true">Player</th> <th data-field="pos" data-halign="center" data-align="center" data-sortable="true">Position</th> <th data-field="slot" data-halign="center" data-align="center" data-sortable="true">Slot</th> <th data-field="points" data-halign="center" data-align="center" data-sortable="true">Points</th> <th data-field="projected" data-halign="center" data-align="center" data-sortable="true">Projected</th> </tr> </thead> </table>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="team-reports"/><category term="2024-25,"/><category term="WeeklyRecap,"/><category term="Week14"/><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Weekly team status report]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Michael’s Managable Team Week 14 Report</title><link href="https://family-fantasy-football.github.io/blog/2024/Week-14-MMT/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Michael’s Managable Team Week 14 Report"/><published>2024-12-10T22:19:38+00:00</published><updated>2024-12-10T22:19:38+00:00</updated><id>https://family-fantasy-football.github.io/blog/2024/Week-14-MMT</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://family-fantasy-football.github.io/blog/2024/Week-14-MMT/"><![CDATA[<h2 id="week-at-a-glance">Week at a Glance</h2> <p>Michael’s Managable Team Lost against Fantasy Guru Kayden 72.52-123.40<br/> Current Standing: #9<br/> Playoff Chances: 0.0%<br/> Lineup Efficiency: 88.6%<br/> Best Performer: CeeDee Lamb (18.40 pts)<br/></p> <pre><code class="language-echarts">{
    "tooltip": {
        "trigger": "item",
        "formatter": "{a} &lt;br/&gt;{b}: {d}%"
    },
    "legend": {
        "orient": "vertical",
        "left": "left",
        "data": [
            "QB",
            "RB",
            "WR",
            "TE",
            "D/ST",
            "K"
        ]
    },
    "series": [
        {
            "name": "Position Points",
            "type": "pie",
            "radius": [
                "50%",
                "70%"
            ],
            "avoidLabelOverlap": false,
            "data": [
                {
                    "value": 13.7,
                    "name": "QB"
                },
                {
                    "value": 20.7,
                    "name": "RB"
                },
                {
                    "value": 30.2,
                    "name": "WR"
                },
                {
                    "value": 7.9,
                    "name": "TE"
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}
</code></pre> <h2 id="player-report">Player Report</h2> <h4 id="trey-benson-rb">Trey Benson (RB)</h4> <p><strong>Injury Status:</strong> Active <br/> <strong>Lineup Slot:</strong> RB/WR/TE <br/> <strong>Details:</strong> While James Conner remains locked in as Arizona’s lead back, Benson has been effective as a change-of-pace option and could be moving ahead of Emari Demercado as the team’s preferred backup. The rookie third-round pick is averaging a healthy 4.6 yards per carry over his 58 totes on the season and has also made the most of his opportunities in the passing game, recording a 6-59-0 receiving line on six targets through 12 appearances. Though Benson played just 10 of the Cardinals’ 71 snaps on offense in the loss, that was still enough to match or surpass Demercado’s snap count (eight) for the third time in the last four games.</p> <h4 id="james-cook-rb">James Cook (RB)</h4> <p><strong>Injury Status:</strong> Active <br/> <strong>Lineup Slot:</strong> RB <br/> <strong>Details:</strong> Josh Allen was the entire Buffalo offense, as he led the team in rushing attempts and yards while also scoring a trio of times on the ground from one yard away. Allen’s usage combined with a negative game script left little opportunity for Cook, who saw his fewest rushing attempts of the season. More concerning was his lack of involvement as a receiver despite Allen taking to the air 37 times. Cook has now failed to reach 50 rushing yards in four of his last seven games.</p> <h4 id="ty-johnson-rb">Ty Johnson (RB)</h4> <p><strong>Injury Status:</strong> Active <br/> <strong>Lineup Slot:</strong> BE <br/> <strong>Details:</strong> Johnson saw five opportunities on the ground for the second-straight game, but the veteran was unable to make much happen with his limited attempts. The 27-year-old played just 16 of the Bills’ 58 offensive snaps, behind starter James Cook (26) and rookie Ray Davis (19). Barring injuries, Johnson should continue to be ignored for fantasy purposes as the Bills square off against the Rams in Week 14.</p> <h4 id="xavier-legette-wr">Xavier Legette (WR)</h4> <p><strong>Injury Status:</strong> Active <br/> <strong>Lineup Slot:</strong> WR <br/> <strong>Details:</strong> The rookie wideout had trouble hanging onto the ball all day, but Legette’s biggest drop came in the fourth quarter when he couldn’t haul in what might have been a game-winning 32-yard touchdown in the final minute. Legette has still caught multiple passes in eight straight games, posting a 26-281-3 line on 46 targets over that stretch. He’ll try to put his volume to better use in Week 15 against the Cowboys.</p> <h4 id="ceedee-lamb-wr">CeeDee Lamb (WR)</h4> <p><strong>Injury Status:</strong> Active <br/> <strong>Lineup Slot:</strong> WR <br/> <strong>Details:</strong> Lamb paced the Cowboys in receptions, receiving yards and targets while also recording an 11-yard touchdown grab on fourth down in the first quarter. The star wideout continued to display solid chemistry with Cooper Rush, and Monday night’s yardage total tied for Lamb’s highest since Rush officially took over starting quarterback duties for Dak Prescott (IR, hamstring) in Week 10. Lamb heads into a favorable Week 15 road matchup against the Panthers with at least six catches in seven of the last eight contests, as well as double-digit targets on five occasions in that span.</p> <h4 id="sam-laporta-te">Sam LaPorta (TE)</h4> <p><strong>Injury Status:</strong> Active <br/> <strong>Lineup Slot:</strong> TE <br/> <strong>Details:</strong> LaPorta tied multiple teammates for second in receptions and finished as the runner-up in receiving yards to Jameson Williams on the night. The talented tight end also matched Tim Patrick for second in targets during what was one of LaPorta’s busiest games yet this season. The catch total was LaPorta’s second highest of 2024, and the targets qualified as a new season high, sending him into a Week 15 home showdown against the Bills on Sunday, Dec. 15 with plenty of momentum.</p> <h4 id="dontayvion-wicks-wr">Dontayvion Wicks (WR)</h4> <p><strong>Injury Status:</strong> Active <br/> <strong>Lineup Slot:</strong> WR <br/> <strong>Details:</strong> Wicks tied Tucker Kraft for second in targets and Christian Watson for the team lead in receptions, although he was a distant second to the latter in receiving yards. Nevertheless, it was notable that Wicks logged four more targets than No. 1 receiver Jayden Reed, who went without a catch. Wicks has back-to-back four-reception outings heading into a Week 15 road matchup against the Seahawks on Sunday night, Dec. 15, but he could be looking at a reduced role if Romeo Doubs (concussion) returns for that game.</p> <h4 id="justin-herbert-qb">Justin Herbert (QB)</h4> <p><strong>Injury Status:</strong> Questionable <br/> <strong>Lineup Slot:</strong> OP <br/> <strong>Details:</strong> Herbert said he “took a shot there and was in some pain, but felt good to go and went back in” during Sunday Night Football. The franchise quarterback could be seen walking with a visible limp after Sunday’s contest, but it doesn’t appear as though he expects to still be dealing with any restrictions versus Tampa Bay in Week 15. Herbert completed 21 of 30 pass attempts for 213 yards and one touchdown versus Kansas City, in addition to taking four carries for 12 yards.</p> <h4 id="demario-douglas-wr">DeMario Douglas (WR)</h4> <p><strong>Injury Status:</strong> Active <br/> <strong>Lineup Slot:</strong> BE <br/> <strong>Details:</strong> Douglas approached the contest listed as questionable, but played through the ankle issue that had limited him at practice. With the Patriots on bye in Week 14, Douglas may be able to avoid the team’s Week 15 injury report. Either way, he figures to maintain enough volume down the stretch to merit lineup attention in PPR formats.</p> <h4 id="rhamondre-stevenson-rb">Rhamondre Stevenson (RB)</h4> <p><strong>Injury Status:</strong> Active <br/> <strong>Lineup Slot:</strong> RB/WR/TE <br/> <strong>Details:</strong> It was a solid performance from Stevenson, but his numbers would have been even better had Antonio Gibson not vultured a red-zone touchdown on an 11-yard run midway through the fourth quarter. Stevenson has gone seven straight games without reaching 80 rushing yards in a game, and the Patriots’ offensive line woes have limited him to a rough 3.1 yards per carry over that stretch. The team’s entire offense will get a breather, and a chance to solve some of its issues, over a Week 14 bye.</p> <h4 id="drake-maye-qb">Drake Maye (QB)</h4> <p><strong>Injury Status:</strong> Active <br/> <strong>Lineup Slot:</strong> QB <br/> <strong>Details:</strong> It was a mostly efficient performance from the rookie quarterback, but Maye’s red-zone INT late in the third quarter ended up being very costly in a one-point loss. He’s been picked off at least once in five straight games, posting a 6:6 TD:INT over that stretch, but growing pains are to be expected from the third overall pick in the 2024 Draft. Maye will get a chance to regroup during the Patriots’ Week 14 bye.</p> <h4 id="kendre-miller-rb">Kendre Miller (RB)</h4> <p><strong>Injury Status:</strong> Active <br/> <strong>Lineup Slot:</strong> BE <br/> <strong>Details:</strong> Making his return to the lineup after a four-game absence due to a hamstring strain, Miller opened the scoring on the afternoon with an eight-yard score late in the first quarter. Alvin Kamara led the Saints’ backfield with 22 touches, but Miller’s 10 topped the five that Jamaal Williams handled, and the second-year back appears to be taking advantage of the clean slate he received when Dennis Allen was let go as head coach. Miller will look to build on this effort in Week 15 against the Commanders.</p> <h4 id="saquon-barkley-rb">Saquon Barkley (RB)</h4> <p><strong>Injury Status:</strong> Active <br/> <strong>Lineup Slot:</strong> RB <br/> <strong>Details:</strong> The star running back reached 100 rushing yards for the fourth straight game and the 10th time this season, in the process setting a new Eagles record with 1,623 rushing yards on the year, topping LeSean McCoy’s 1,607 yards from 2013. Barkley remains on track to top 2,000 yards on the season, and Eric Dickerson’s NFL record of 2,105 yards is firmly in his sights. Barkley will look to keep rolling in Week 15 against the Steelers.</p> <h4 id="jaylen-warren-rb">Jaylen Warren (RB)</h4> <p><strong>Injury Status:</strong> Active <br/> <strong>Lineup Slot:</strong> BE <br/> <strong>Details:</strong> Warren was on the field for 52 percent of the Steelers’ offensive snaps Sunday, outpacing Najee Harris’ 42 percent and Cordarrelle Patterson’s 14 percent. Warren responded by topping 50 yards from scrimmage for a seventh consecutive game, but Harris was the only Pittsburgh back to reach the end zone with a one-yard touchdown run in the second quarter. Warren has carved out a somewhat consistent fantasy role, but his ceiling is limited as long as he’s sharing the backfield with Harris.</p> <h2 id="current-lineup">Current Lineup</h2> <table data-click-to-select="true" data-height="630" data-search="false" data-toggle="table" data-url="/assets/json/team_rosters/Week_14_2024_MMT_roster.json"> <thead> <tr> <th data-field="player_name" data-halign="left" data-align="left" data-sortable="true">Player</th> <th data-field="pos" data-halign="center" data-align="center" data-sortable="true">Position</th> <th data-field="slot" data-halign="center" data-align="center" data-sortable="true">Slot</th> <th data-field="points" data-halign="center" data-align="center" data-sortable="true">Points</th> <th data-field="projected" data-halign="center" data-align="center" data-sortable="true">Projected</th> </tr> </thead> </table> <p><br/><br/></p> <h2 id="optimal-lineup">Optimal Lineup</h2> <table data-click-to-select="true" data-height="630" data-search="false" data-toggle="table" data-url="/assets/json/team_rosters/Week_14_2024_MMT_optimal.json"> <thead> <tr> <th data-field="player_name" data-halign="left" data-align="left" data-sortable="true">Player</th> <th data-field="pos" data-halign="center" data-align="center" data-sortable="true">Position</th> <th data-field="slot" data-halign="center" data-align="center" data-sortable="true">Slot</th> <th data-field="points" data-halign="center" data-align="center" data-sortable="true">Points</th> <th data-field="projected" data-halign="center" data-align="center" data-sortable="true">Projected</th> </tr> </thead> </table>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="team-reports"/><category term="2024-25,"/><category term="WeeklyRecap,"/><category term="Week14"/><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Weekly team status report]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Pink Pony Club Week 14 Report</title><link href="https://family-fantasy-football.github.io/blog/2024/Week-14-PONY/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Pink Pony Club Week 14 Report"/><published>2024-12-10T22:19:38+00:00</published><updated>2024-12-10T22:19:38+00:00</updated><id>https://family-fantasy-football.github.io/blog/2024/Week-14-PONY</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://family-fantasy-football.github.io/blog/2024/Week-14-PONY/"><![CDATA[<h2 id="week-at-a-glance">Week at a Glance</h2> <p>Pink Pony Club Won against Tom and Jerry 169.20-154.40<br/> Current Standing: #1<br/> Playoff Chances: 100.0%<br/> Lineup Efficiency: 86.3%<br/> Best Performer: Isaac Guerendo (25.80 pts)<br/></p> <pre><code class="language-echarts">{
    "tooltip": {
        "trigger": "item",
        "formatter": "{a} &lt;br/&gt;{b}: {d}%"
    },
    "legend": {
        "orient": "vertical",
        "left": "left",
        "data": [
            "QB",
            "RB",
            "WR",
            "TE",
            "D/ST",
            "K"
        ]
    },
    "series": [
        {
            "name": "Position Points",
            "type": "pie",
            "radius": [
                "50%",
                "70%"
            ],
            "avoidLabelOverlap": false,
            "data": [
                {
                    "value": 39.5,
                    "name": "QB"
                },
                {
                    "value": 85.0,
                    "name": "RB"
                },
                {
                    "value": 36.2,
                    "name": "WR"
                },
                {
                    "value": 8.5,
                    "name": "TE"
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}
</code></pre> <h2 id="player-report">Player Report</h2> <h4 id="james-conner-rb">James Conner (RB)</h4> <p><strong>Injury Status:</strong> Active <br/> <strong>Lineup Slot:</strong> RB/WR/TE <br/> <strong>Details:</strong> Conner caught a two-yard touchdown pass late in the third quarter on an underhand pass from Kyler Murray for the veteran running back’s first receiving touchdown of the season. This was also Conner’s highest rushing yardage total since Week 9, as he had only 109 yards on the ground in three games in between. Conner will look to build off this bounce-back effort in a favorable Week 15 matchup against the 3-10 Patriots.</p> <h4 id="rashod-bateman-wr">Rashod Bateman (WR)</h4> <p><strong>Injury Status:</strong> Questionable <br/> <strong>Lineup Slot:</strong> BE <br/> <strong>Details:</strong> Bateman was forced out of Baltimore’s loss to the Eagles in Week 13 due to what head coach John Harbaugh described as knee soreness, so it’s encouraging to see him back on the practice field. The Ravens’ bye week was well-timed for Bateman, who will continue to work at ramping up his health, with the target of retaking the field Sunday versus the Giants. Wednesday’s first official practice report of the week will reveal whether Bateman is practicing in full or being capped as a limited participant.</p> <h4 id="khalil-shakir-wr">Khalil Shakir (WR)</h4> <p><strong>Injury Status:</strong> Active <br/> <strong>Lineup Slot:</strong> BE <br/> <strong>Details:</strong> Shakir was a non-factor in the first half, recording only 21 yards on two targets. He came alive as the offenses matched blows in the final two quarters, however, highlighted by a 51-yard touchdown grab, which came primarily after the catch as he bounced off defenders. On Buffalo’s next possession, Shakir caught a 34-yard pass from Josh Allen that finished just one yard shy of another trip to the end zone. This was Shakir’s second 100-yard performance of the season and his first touchdown since Week 3.</p> <h4 id="adam-thielen-wr">Adam Thielen (WR)</h4> <p><strong>Injury Status:</strong> Active <br/> <strong>Lineup Slot:</strong> BE <br/> <strong>Details:</strong> It’s the first time this season that Thielen has topped 100 yards, with his last such performance coming in Week 6 of the 2023 campaign. The veteran wideout has posted a 20-258-1 line on 25 targets over three games since returning from a hamstring injury, giving him significant momentum heading into a Week 15 matchup against the Cowboys.</p> <h4 id="jameis-winston-qb">Jameis Winston (QB)</h4> <p><strong>Injury Status:</strong> Active <br/> <strong>Lineup Slot:</strong> BE <br/> <strong>Details:</strong> Stefanski noted that despite being eliminated from playoff contention, the Browns’ focus is “just trying to find ways to get a win,” and to that end, Winston is seen as a better candidate to direct the offense than backup Dorian Thompson-Robinson. Winston – who has logged a 2-4 record as the team’s starter – thus is slated to face the 12-1 Chiefs this weekend following a Week 14 outing in which he completed 24 of 41 passes for 212 yards with two touchdowns and two interceptions in a 27-14 loss to the Steelers.</p> <h4 id="elijah-moore-wr">Elijah Moore (WR)</h4> <p><strong>Injury Status:</strong> Active <br/> <strong>Lineup Slot:</strong> BE <br/> <strong>Details:</strong> Moore was expected to benefit from condensed targets in the absence of Cedric Tillman (concussion). That wasn’t the case against the Steelers, however, as Jameis Winston targeted seven different pass catchers multiple times. That left Moore with a mediocre line, and he’s now had 35 or fewer receiving yards in two of his last four games.</p> <h4 id="jahmyr-gibbs-rb">Jahmyr Gibbs (RB)</h4> <p><strong>Injury Status:</strong> Active <br/> <strong>Lineup Slot:</strong> RB <br/> <strong>Details:</strong> Gibbs and backfield mate David Montgomery struggled to find consistent running room, and 20 of Gibbs’ rushing yards actually came on one carry. However, the second-year back tied Tim Patrick for the lead in receptions and recorded his second receiving touchdown of the season on a two-yard catch just before halftime. Gibbs now has four total touchdowns (three rushing, one receiving) over the last four games heading into a Week 15 home clash against the Bills on Sunday, Dec. 15.</p> <h4 id="evan-engram-te">Evan Engram (TE)</h4> <p><strong>Injury Status:</strong> Active <br/> <strong>Lineup Slot:</strong> BE <br/> <strong>Details:</strong> Engram’s six targets were good for second on the team and also marked his fifth straight game with at least that many opportunities. However, his longest catch went for just 11 yards as the Jacksonville offense struggled to generate explosive plays. Engram has now been held below 40 yards in half of his last eight games.</p> <h4 id="brian-thomas-jr-wr">Brian Thomas Jr. (WR)</h4> <p><strong>Injury Status:</strong> Active <br/> <strong>Lineup Slot:</strong> WR <br/> <strong>Details:</strong> Thomas was one of the few players to get going in an ugly offensive showing from both teams. He delivered splash plays of 31 and 21 yards on the Jaguars’ only touchdown drive of the game, setting up a rushing score for Tank Bigsby. Despite otherwise being limited to short gains, Thomas has at least 75 receiving yards and four receptions in each of his last three games.</p> <h4 id="kyren-williams-rb">Kyren Williams (RB)</h4> <p><strong>Injury Status:</strong> Active <br/> <strong>Lineup Slot:</strong> RB <br/> <strong>Details:</strong> Williams saw a season-high 29 rushing attempts, his first time topping 20 carries since Week 9. He wasn’t very efficient, as he averaged only 3.0 yards per carry with his longest run going for 12 yards. However, volume was enough to carry Williams’ fantasy performance, and he also supplemented his yardage with three- and seven-yard rushing scores. He now has a touchdown in three straight contests and has at least 80 rushing yards in three of his last four games.</p> <h4 id="tyrone-tracy-jr-rb">Tyrone Tracy Jr. (RB)</h4> <p><strong>Injury Status:</strong> Active <br/> <strong>Lineup Slot:</strong> BE <br/> <strong>Details:</strong> The rookie running back punched in a one-yard score late in the fourth quarter, giving Tracy his fifth rushing TD in the last eight games. Over that stretch, he’s amassed 680 scrimmage yards while solidifying his spot at the top of the Giants’ backfield depth chart. Tracy faces a tough matchup on the ground in Week 15 against the Ravens.</p> <h4 id="jalen-hurts-qb">Jalen Hurts (QB)</h4> <p><strong>Injury Status:</strong> Active <br/> <strong>Lineup Slot:</strong> QB <br/> <strong>Details:</strong> For the third straight game and the sixth time this season, Hurts failed to throw for 200 yards, with Sunday’s total being his lowest of the year. He made up for it by producing three TDs, including a four-yard strike to Grant Calcaterra early in the fourth quarter for what proved to be the winning score. Hurts has 13 rushing touchdowns on the season, leaving him two short of tying the NFL quarterback record of 15 he shares with Josh Allen, a mark they both reached in 2023. Hurts faces a stingy secondary in Week 15 against the Steelers.</p> <h4 id="isaac-guerendo-rb">Isaac Guerendo (RB)</h4> <p><strong>Injury Status:</strong> Questionable <br/> <strong>Lineup Slot:</strong> RB/WR/TE <br/> <strong>Details:</strong> Guerendo will go down as a non-participant on the 49ers’ second injury report of the week. With the 49ers facing a quick turnaround from Sunday’s win over the Bears with a Thursday night matchup with the Rams, the rookie running back looks like he may be facing an uphill battle to gain clearance after exiting the Week 14 contest with a sprained foot. Before departing with the injury, Guerendo showed well in his first NFL start, carrying 15 times for 78 yards and two touchdowns to go with two catches for 50 yards. If the Louisville product ends up missing Thursday’s game, Patrick Taylor, Ke’Shawn Vaughn and Israel Abanikanda would represent the 49ers’ available options at running back.</p> <h4 id="deebo-samuel-sr-wr">Deebo Samuel Sr. (WR)</h4> <p><strong>Injury Status:</strong> Active <br/> <strong>Lineup Slot:</strong> BE <br/> <strong>Details:</strong> Samuel was seemingly the only key member of the 49ers not to wake up in Sunday’s landslide victory over the lowly Bears. The dual-threat star couldn’t get anything going on the ground while George Kittle (6-151-0) and Jauan Jennings (7-90-2) did all the work in the passing game. Samuel is currently mired in a four-game slump that has resulted in 22 or fewer receiving yards in each contest during that span. This Thursday’s crucial matchup against the Rams – who just gave up 42 points in a win over the Bills – is a prime opportunity for Samuel to look like his former self. If he turns in yet another stinker, managers may have to consider what was once unthinkable – benching the star player due to poor performance as many fantasy leagues enter the playoffs.</p> <h4 id="cade-otton-te">Cade Otton (TE)</h4> <p><strong>Injury Status:</strong> Active <br/> <strong>Lineup Slot:</strong> TE <br/> <strong>Details:</strong> The third-year tight end finished with a team-high receiving yardage figure and ranked second in receptions as well. The highlight of Otton’s afternoon was a 44-yard reception in the fourth quarter that helped set up the Buccaneers’ final touchdown of the game, and Sunday marked his most productive showing since a Week 9, 77-yard effort against the Chiefs. Otton should continue to be an integral part of the Buccaneers’ shorthanded passing attack in a Week 15 road matchup against the Chargers.</p> <h4 id="jayden-daniels-qb">Jayden Daniels (QB)</h4> <p><strong>Injury Status:</strong> Active <br/> <strong>Lineup Slot:</strong> OP <br/> <strong>Details:</strong> Daniels gave the Commanders a 14-0 lead with a three-yard rushing touchdown, then doubled that first-half advantage with touchdown passes of 16 and three yards to Terry McLaurin. The rookie second overall pick missed only one of his 15 first-half pass attempts but was picked off in the third quarter as the Titans cut what was once a 28-point Washington lead to 28-13 heading into the fourth quarter. He bounced back with a four-yard touchdown pass to Zach Ertz early in the fourth to snuff out any hopes of a Tennessee comeback. Daniels has thrown 15 touchdown passes and run in six touchdowns to lead the Commanders to an 8-5 record heading into their Week 14 bye.</p> <h4 id="terry-mclaurin-wr">Terry McLaurin (WR)</h4> <p><strong>Injury Status:</strong> Active <br/> <strong>Lineup Slot:</strong> WR <br/> <strong>Details:</strong> McLaurin extended Washington’s advantage to 21-0 with a 16-yard touchdown catch in the final minute of the first quarter, then caught a three-yard touchdown in the second quarter. After getting off to slow starts in recent weeks, McLaurin piled up six catches for 52 yards and two touchdowns in the first half of this lopsided win. He wasn’t heavily involved in the second half as the Commanders rode their running game while nursing a hefty lead. McLaurin has three multi-touchdown games and nine receiving scores overall heading into Washington’s Week 14 bye.</p> <h2 id="current-lineup">Current Lineup</h2> <table data-click-to-select="true" data-height="630" data-search="false" data-toggle="table" data-url="/assets/json/team_rosters/Week_14_2024_PONY_roster.json"> <thead> <tr> <th data-field="player_name" data-halign="left" data-align="left" data-sortable="true">Player</th> <th data-field="pos" data-halign="center" data-align="center" data-sortable="true">Position</th> <th data-field="slot" data-halign="center" data-align="center" data-sortable="true">Slot</th> <th data-field="points" data-halign="center" data-align="center" data-sortable="true">Points</th> <th data-field="projected" data-halign="center" data-align="center" data-sortable="true">Projected</th> </tr> </thead> </table> <p><br/><br/></p> <h2 id="optimal-lineup">Optimal Lineup</h2> <table data-click-to-select="true" data-height="630" data-search="false" data-toggle="table" data-url="/assets/json/team_rosters/Week_14_2024_PONY_optimal.json"> <thead> <tr> <th data-field="player_name" data-halign="left" data-align="left" data-sortable="true">Player</th> <th data-field="pos" data-halign="center" data-align="center" data-sortable="true">Position</th> <th data-field="slot" data-halign="center" data-align="center" data-sortable="true">Slot</th> <th data-field="points" data-halign="center" data-align="center" data-sortable="true">Points</th> <th data-field="projected" data-halign="center" data-align="center" data-sortable="true">Projected</th> </tr> </thead> </table>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="team-reports"/><category term="2024-25,"/><category term="WeeklyRecap,"/><category term="Week14"/><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Weekly team status report]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Hit and Ruggs Week 14 Report</title><link href="https://family-fantasy-football.github.io/blog/2024/Week-14-RRT/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Hit and Ruggs Week 14 Report"/><published>2024-12-10T22:19:38+00:00</published><updated>2024-12-10T22:19:38+00:00</updated><id>https://family-fantasy-football.github.io/blog/2024/Week-14-RRT</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://family-fantasy-football.github.io/blog/2024/Week-14-RRT/"><![CDATA[<h2 id="week-at-a-glance">Week at a Glance</h2> <p>Hit and Ruggs Won against To Infinity and Bijan! 131.44-103.98<br/> Current Standing: #6<br/> Playoff Chances: 0.0%<br/> Lineup Efficiency: 86.7%<br/> Best Performer: Justin Jefferson (28.70 pts)<br/></p> <pre><code class="language-echarts">{
    "tooltip": {
        "trigger": "item",
        "formatter": "{a} &lt;br/&gt;{b}: {d}%"
    },
    "legend": {
        "orient": "vertical",
        "left": "left",
        "data": [
            "QB",
            "RB",
            "WR",
            "TE",
            "D/ST",
            "K"
        ]
    },
    "series": [
        {
            "name": "Position Points",
            "type": "pie",
            "radius": [
                "50%",
                "70%"
            ],
            "avoidLabelOverlap": false,
            "data": [
                {
                    "value": 35.3,
                    "name": "QB"
                },
                {
                    "value": 15.9,
                    "name": "RB"
                },
                {
                    "value": 69.7,
                    "name": "WR"
                },
                {
                    "value": 10.5,
                    "name": "TE"
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}
</code></pre> <h2 id="player-report">Player Report</h2> <h4 id="marvin-harrison-jr-wr">Marvin Harrison Jr. (WR)</h4> <p><strong>Injury Status:</strong> Active <br/> <strong>Lineup Slot:</strong> RB/WR/TE <br/> <strong>Details:</strong> Harrison has reached 50 receiving yards only five times in his up-and-down rookie season. His eight targets against Seattle ranked second behind Trey McBride’s 14, and Harrison’s 20 targets over the last two games are the most he has seen in a two-game span. While there’s reason for long-term optimism with the fourth overall pick in the 2024 NFL Draft, including Harrison’s team-leading total of seven receiving touchdowns, he can’t be viewed as a surefire fantasy starter in most formats when the Cardinals host the Patriots in Week 15.</p> <h4 id="trey-mcbride-te">Trey McBride (TE)</h4> <p><strong>Injury Status:</strong> Active <br/> <strong>Lineup Slot:</strong> RB/WR/TE <br/> <strong>Details:</strong> After producing 12 catches in each of his previous two games, including in Week 12 against Seattle, McBride was blanked on three first-half targets. He returned to his productive ways in the second half to finish with the team lead in targets, catches and receiving yards. McBride has secured his second consecutive 80-catch season with 80 receptions for 851 yards heading into a Week 15 home game against the Patriots.</p> <h4 id="diontae-johnson-wr">Diontae Johnson (WR)</h4> <p><strong>Injury Status:</strong> Suspension <br/> <strong>Lineup Slot:</strong> BE <br/> <strong>Details:</strong> General manager Eric DeCosta said in a statement that the decision to suspend Johnson stemmed from the receiver’s refusal to enter the game in last Sunday’s 24-19 loss to the Eagles. Since being acquired from the Panthers in late October, Johnson has played a total of 39 offensive snaps and has just one catch for six yards across five contests with Baltimore. Tylan Wallace has even leapfrogged Johnson on the depth chart as the team’s No. 4 receiver, and the suspension likely won’t help Johnson’s chances of regaining playing time when he’s eligible to return to action Week 16 versus Pittsburgh.</p> <h4 id="ray-davis-rb">Ray Davis (RB)</h4> <p><strong>Injury Status:</strong> Active <br/> <strong>Lineup Slot:</strong> BE <br/> <strong>Details:</strong> Davis was involved early, scoring a five-yard rushing touchdown in the first quarter, but most of his yardage came later in the game after the result was no longer in doubt. James Cook (14 carries for 107 yards and a touchdown) paced Buffalo’s backfield as usual, but Davis benefited from a run-heavy game plan in snowy conditions. Davis will continue to work as the team’s No. 2 running back behind Cook in Week 14 against the Rams.</p> <h4 id="rome-odunze-wr">Rome Odunze (WR)</h4> <p><strong>Injury Status:</strong> Active <br/> <strong>Lineup Slot:</strong> BE <br/> <strong>Details:</strong> Odunze cashed in a pair of garbage-time touchdowns in Sunday’s blowout loss for the first multi-score game of his young career. When the rookie scored during the contest shouldn’t matter to fantasy managers, who had witnessed just one trip to the end zone over the wideout’s previous 12 contests. Odunze’s inconsistency in Chicago’s flailing offense keeps him from relevance in shallower formats ahead of next Monday’s tilt against Minnesota.</p> <h4 id="chase-brown-rb">Chase Brown (RB)</h4> <p><strong>Injury Status:</strong> Active <br/> <strong>Lineup Slot:</strong> BE <br/> <strong>Details:</strong> Brown scored his ninth touchdown of the season off a lengthy reception Monday, but the play needed a successful challenge to overrule the referees marking the back out at the three-yard line. The 24-year-old got a highlight moment by leaping into the Salvation Army holiday pot at AT&amp;T Stadium, paying homage to Ezekiel Elliott’s touchdown celebration back in 2016. Brown has scored all nine of his touchdowns over the Bengals’ last 10 games, making him a strong fantasy asset heading in to a soft matchup against the Titans on Sunday.</p> <h4 id="jared-goff-qb">Jared Goff (QB)</h4> <p><strong>Injury Status:</strong> Active <br/> <strong>Lineup Slot:</strong> QB <br/> <strong>Details:</strong> Goff got the Lions off and running with a crisp 11-play, 70-yard march that culminated in a David Montgomery three-yard walk-in rushing touchdown on the first possession of the contest. The veteran signal-caller would go on to struggle some during the rest of the first half, although he did get Detroit back in the end zone before halftime with a two-yard scoring toss to Jahmyr Gibbs. Goff would throw his one interception on a slant during Detroit’s first drive of the second half, a pick that led to a Packers touchdown. Nevertheless, he would redeem himself with three- and one-yard scoring tosses to Tim Patrick, while recording a pair of clutch completions during the game-winning drive late in the fourth quarter. Goff’s interception broke a three-game streak without a pick, but he still boasts a 9:1 TD:INT over his last four contests heading into a Week 15 home showdown against Josh Allen and the Bills on Sunday, Dec. 15.</p> <h4 id="cooper-kupp-wr">Cooper Kupp (WR)</h4> <p><strong>Injury Status:</strong> Active <br/> <strong>Lineup Slot:</strong> WR <br/> <strong>Details:</strong> Kupp was overshadowed by Puka Nacua’s 162-yard performance, but he had a solid showing of his own while operating as the Rams’ big-play threat. He had long receptions of 37 and 24 yards and also found the end zone on a 17-yard reception late in the third quarter. After combining to record only 77 yards across his last two games, this was a needed bounceback performance for Kupp, though he is still clearly operating behind Nacua as the second option in the passing game.</p> <h4 id="jaylen-waddle-wr">Jaylen Waddle (WR)</h4> <p><strong>Injury Status:</strong> Active <br/> <strong>Lineup Slot:</strong> WR <br/> <strong>Details:</strong> Waddle caught the game-tying two-point conversion with 9:04 left in the fourth quarter, and Miami tied the game again with a field goal in the final seconds before winning it in overtime. The Dolphins’ passing game has heated up heading into a Week 15 trip to Houston. Tua Tagovailoa has topped 300 passing yards in each of his last three starts, with Waddle accounting for 296 receiving yards and a touchdown over that span.</p> <h4 id="devon-achane-rb">De’Von Achane (RB)</h4> <p><strong>Injury Status:</strong> Active <br/> <strong>Lineup Slot:</strong> RB <br/> <strong>Details:</strong> Achane finally opened the scoring with a two-yard touchdown run after mustering just one yard on three previous rushing attempts inside the 3-yard line. He later went to the medical tent to be evaluated for a concussion after taking a big hit, per CBS sideline reporter Melanie Collins, and Achane spent a significant chunk of the first half on the sideline before checking back in on Miami’s final drive before halftime. He failed to find much running room but remained heavily involved as a pass catcher, as has been customary when quarterback Tua Tagovailoa plays. Heading into a Week 15 trip to Houston, Achane has racked up at least six receptions in six of Tagovailoa’s nine starts this season.</p> <h4 id="justin-jefferson-wr">Justin Jefferson (WR)</h4> <p><strong>Injury Status:</strong> Active <br/> <strong>Lineup Slot:</strong> WR <br/> <strong>Details:</strong> Jefferson finished just a reception and receiving yard shy of tying Jordan Addison for the team lead in both categories, but he enjoyed a highly efficient afternoon during which he finished with his third-highest receiving yardage total of the campaign. Jefferson also crossed the goal line for the first time since Week 7 with 12- and 52-yard touchdown grabs in the second and third quarters, respectively. The standout receiver has at least 81 receiving yards in three of the last four games heading into a Week 15 home divisional clash against the Bears on Monday night, Dec. 16.</p> <h4 id="sam-darnold-qb">Sam Darnold (QB)</h4> <p><strong>Injury Status:</strong> Active <br/> <strong>Lineup Slot:</strong> BE <br/> <strong>Details:</strong> Darnold and the Vikings punted after seven plays on their first drive, but the offensive showcase began on Minnesota’s second possession in the form of a 49-yard touchdown pass to Jordan Addison. Darnold encountered little resistance the rest of the way while accumulating single-game career highs in passing yards and touchdowns, hitting Justin Jefferson (12 yards, 52 yards) and Addison (11 yards, six yards) for his other four scoring tosses. Darnold now has multiple touchdown-pass tallies without an interception in four straight games, as well as a pair of 300-yard efforts in the last three contests. The veteran quarterback’s resurgent season’s next chapter unfolds at home against the Bears in a Week 15 Monday night matchup Dec. 16.</p> <h4 id="antonio-gibson-rb">Antonio Gibson (RB)</h4> <p><strong>Injury Status:</strong> Active <br/> <strong>Lineup Slot:</strong> RB <br/> <strong>Details:</strong> The fifth-year RB posted his best rushing yards total since Week 2, and Gibson capped his big performance with an 11-yard TD run in the fourth quarter that gave the Patriots a 24-17 lead. The trip to the end zone was the first of the season for the former Washington back – his last touchdown came in Week 16 of 2023. He hasn’t seen double-double digits touches while Rhamondre Stevenson has been healthy since Week 2, but Gibson’s ability to turn small holes into big gains could lead to a bigger role in the offense on the other side of New England’s Week 14 bye.</p> <h4 id="wandale-robinson-wr">Wan’Dale Robinson (WR)</h4> <p><strong>Injury Status:</strong> Active <br/> <strong>Lineup Slot:</strong> BE <br/> <strong>Details:</strong> The slot receiver led the Giants in targets but did little with the volume, finishing third on the team in receiving yards and fourth in catches. Robinson has caught multiple passes in every game this season, but he hasn’t scored a touchdown since Week 5 and hasn’t topped 60 yards since Week 4. He’ll try to do more with his opportunities in Week 15 against the Ravens.</p> <h4 id="breece-hall-rb">Breece Hall (RB)</h4> <p><strong>Injury Status:</strong> Questionable <br/> <strong>Lineup Slot:</strong> BE <br/> <strong>Details:</strong> questionable</p> <h4 id="allen-lazard-wr">Allen Lazard (WR)</h4> <p><strong>Injury Status:</strong> Active <br/> <strong>Lineup Slot:</strong> IR <br/> <strong>Details:</strong> Seeing his first action since Week 7, Lazard played 78 percent of snaps on offense, so his lack of production wasn’t due to a lack of playing time. He’s a distant third on the Jets’ wide receiver depth chart behind Garrett Wilson and Davante Adams, who combined for 223 yards and a touchdown on 21 targets against the Dolphins. Lazard will be a touchdown-dependent Week 15 fantasy option against a Jaguars defense that’s giving up 26.5 points per game.</p> <h4 id="braelon-allen-rb">Braelon Allen (RB)</h4> <p><strong>Injury Status:</strong> Active <br/> <strong>Lineup Slot:</strong> BE <br/> <strong>Details:</strong> Allen split time evenly with Isaiah Davis in the absence of lead back Breece Hall (knee), as both rookie running backs had 16 combined carries and targets. The biggest play between the two was a 17-yard touchdown run by Davis in the second quarter, while Allen has still scored only once since his two-touchdown performance back in Week 2. If Hall remains unavailable in Week 15, both Allen and Davis would have substantial fantasy value against the vulnerable Jacksonville defense.</p> <h4 id="dallas-goedert-te">Dallas Goedert (TE)</h4> <p><strong>Injury Status:</strong> Injured Reserve <br/> <strong>Lineup Slot:</strong> TE <br/> <strong>Details:</strong> This was reported earlier by various sources, but it was officially confirmed by the team later in the day. Grant Calcaterra and C.J. Uzomah will be tasked with taking on the work vacated by Goedert, who will be eligible to return during the team’s final week of the regular season.</p> <h4 id="geno-smith-qb">Geno Smith (QB)</h4> <p><strong>Injury Status:</strong> Active <br/> <strong>Lineup Slot:</strong> OP <br/> <strong>Details:</strong> Smith kept the chains moving against a division rival with efficient play from the pocket while going 7-for-15 on third-down attempts, helping his team hold onto sole possession of first place in the NFC West following the victory. The veteran signal-caller let Seattle’s rushing attack do the heavy lifting against Arizona on the back of Zach Charbonnet’s standout effort (22-134-2). Smith hasn’t been asked to do much over the Seahawks’ current win streak, but he could be in store for more work against a high-powered Packers offense next Sunday.</p> <h2 id="current-lineup">Current Lineup</h2> <table data-click-to-select="true" data-height="630" data-search="false" data-toggle="table" data-url="/assets/json/team_rosters/Week_14_2024_RRT_roster.json"> <thead> <tr> <th data-field="player_name" data-halign="left" data-align="left" data-sortable="true">Player</th> <th data-field="pos" data-halign="center" data-align="center" data-sortable="true">Position</th> <th data-field="slot" data-halign="center" data-align="center" data-sortable="true">Slot</th> <th data-field="points" data-halign="center" data-align="center" data-sortable="true">Points</th> <th data-field="projected" data-halign="center" data-align="center" data-sortable="true">Projected</th> </tr> </thead> </table> <p><br/><br/></p> <h2 id="optimal-lineup">Optimal Lineup</h2> <table data-click-to-select="true" data-height="630" data-search="false" data-toggle="table" data-url="/assets/json/team_rosters/Week_14_2024_RRT_optimal.json"> <thead> <tr> <th data-field="player_name" data-halign="left" data-align="left" data-sortable="true">Player</th> <th data-field="pos" data-halign="center" data-align="center" data-sortable="true">Position</th> <th data-field="slot" data-halign="center" data-align="center" data-sortable="true">Slot</th> <th data-field="points" data-halign="center" data-align="center" data-sortable="true">Points</th> <th data-field="projected" data-halign="center" data-align="center" data-sortable="true">Projected</th> </tr> </thead> </table>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="team-reports"/><category term="2024-25,"/><category term="WeeklyRecap,"/><category term="Week14"/><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Weekly team status report]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">To Infinity and Bijan! Week 14 Report</title><link href="https://family-fantasy-football.github.io/blog/2024/Week-14-TIB/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="To Infinity and Bijan! Week 14 Report"/><published>2024-12-10T22:19:38+00:00</published><updated>2024-12-10T22:19:38+00:00</updated><id>https://family-fantasy-football.github.io/blog/2024/Week-14-TIB</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://family-fantasy-football.github.io/blog/2024/Week-14-TIB/"><![CDATA[<h2 id="week-at-a-glance">Week at a Glance</h2> <p>To Infinity and Bijan! Lost against Hit and Ruggs 103.98-131.44<br/> Current Standing: #5<br/> Playoff Chances: 0.0%<br/> Lineup Efficiency: 86.7%<br/> Best Performer: Bijan Robinson (19.10 pts)<br/></p> <pre><code class="language-echarts">{
    "tooltip": {
        "trigger": "item",
        "formatter": "{a} &lt;br/&gt;{b}: {d}%"
    },
    "legend": {
        "orient": "vertical",
        "left": "left",
        "data": [
            "QB",
            "RB",
            "WR",
            "TE",
            "D/ST",
            "K"
        ]
    },
    "series": [
        {
            "name": "Position Points",
            "type": "pie",
            "radius": [
                "50%",
                "70%"
            ],
            "avoidLabelOverlap": false,
            "data": [
                {
                    "value": 33.6,
                    "name": "QB"
                },
                {
                    "value": 19.9,
                    "name": "RB"
                },
                {
                    "value": 50.5,
                    "name": "WR"
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}
</code></pre> <h2 id="player-report">Player Report</h2> <h4 id="darnell-mooney-wr">Darnell Mooney (WR)</h4> <p><strong>Injury Status:</strong> Active <br/> <strong>Lineup Slot:</strong> RB/WR/TE <br/> <strong>Details:</strong> Mooney led the Falcons in receiving yards on the afternoon with a figure that also qualified as a career high. The speedster was a menace to the Vikings’ defense throughout the contest, recording catches of 28, 24 and 49 yards in the first half alone. Mooney also had 18- and 14-yard grabs in the second half, and his prolific performance was a sorely needed one after the veteran wideout had posted just a 5-47 line over the previous two games. Mooney heads into a Week 15 road battle against the Raiders on Monday night, Dec. 16 just 117 receiving yards shy of his second career 1,000-yard campaign.</p> <h4 id="bijan-robinson-rb">Bijan Robinson (RB)</h4> <p><strong>Injury Status:</strong> Active <br/> <strong>Lineup Slot:</strong> RB <br/> <strong>Details:</strong> Facing a Vikings defense that had been one of the best in the league at stopping the run, Robinson put together a workman-like effort that saw him grind out 4.2 yards per tote with the second-highest carry total of his career. Robinson also recorded a rushing touchdown for the second consecutive game – and fourth time in the last four contests – on a 13-yard run late in the third quarter, and he’s now eclipsed 90 rushing yards in three of his last four games as well. Robinson’s workload pushed him over the 20-carry mark in consecutive games for the first time in his young career, affording him plenty of momentum as the fantasy playoffs begin and he heads into a favorable Week 15 road matchup against the Raiders on Monday night, Dec. 16.</p> <h4 id="dalton-kincaid-te">Dalton Kincaid (TE)</h4> <p><strong>Injury Status:</strong> Questionable <br/> <strong>Lineup Slot:</strong> BE <br/> <strong>Details:</strong> questionable</p> <h4 id="cole-kmet-te">Cole Kmet (TE)</h4> <p><strong>Injury Status:</strong> Active <br/> <strong>Lineup Slot:</strong> TE <br/> <strong>Details:</strong> Four days removed from earning 10 targets during a defeat to the Vikings, Kmet fell back to what he more or less has received most weeks this season (26 targets in the nine games in which he didn’t see double-digit looks). Elsewhere in the Bears’ skill ranks Thursday, DJ Moore led the way by a large margin with an 8-97-1 line on 16 targets, Keenan Allen scored twice among his five catches for 73 yards on eight targets, and Rome Odunze (2-25-0 on six targets) and D’Andre Swift (2-35-0 on three targets) also got in the act. With that knowledge, Kmet likely will resume his modest role in Chicago’s offense in his next game Sunday, Dec. 8 in San Francisco.</p> <h4 id="mike-gesicki-te">Mike Gesicki (TE)</h4> <p><strong>Injury Status:</strong> Active <br/> <strong>Lineup Slot:</strong> BE <br/> <strong>Details:</strong> Gesicki has caught all eight of his targets since the Bengals Week 12 bye, resulting in 77 yards. Those numbers scratch the surface for those in deeper formats but leave much to be desired as a standard-league tight end. Gesicki and the Bengals have a road tilt scheduled against the Titans in Week 15.</p> <h4 id="tee-higgins-wr">Tee Higgins (WR)</h4> <p><strong>Injury Status:</strong> Active <br/> <strong>Lineup Slot:</strong> WR <br/> <strong>Details:</strong> Higgins was overshadowed by superstar Ja’Marr Chase’s standout performance (14-177-2), resulting in paltry fantasy numbers for Higgins managers Monday and his lowest catch total of the season. This isn’t the first time this has happened, and it likely won’t be the last, but fantasy GMs must keep faith in the talented No. 2 option for Cincinnati. Higgins could be in store for a bounce-back performance against the lowly Titans on Sunday.</p> <h4 id="troy-franklin-wr">Troy Franklin (WR)</h4> <p><strong>Injury Status:</strong> Active <br/> <strong>Lineup Slot:</strong> BE <br/> <strong>Details:</strong> Franklin has now recorded just two receptions in three straight games, while playing around 42 percent of the Broncos’ offensive snaps per game in that span. The rookie wideout has played in a secondary role in Denver’s offense as he continues to develop in head coach Sean Payton’s system. Franklin’s chemistry with quarterback Bo Nix from their time at Oregon has helped him to garner steady targets throughout the season, but he isn’t seeing enough volume to be trusted for fantasy purposes. The 21-year-old heads into the Broncos’ Week 14 bye with a total of 21 catches for 218 yards and two touchdowns through 12 games. The Broncos will return from the bye to host the Colts on Dec. 15.</p> <h4 id="amon-ra-st-brown-wr">Amon-Ra St. Brown (WR)</h4> <p><strong>Injury Status:</strong> Active <br/> <strong>Lineup Slot:</strong> WR <br/> <strong>Details:</strong> As had been the case in four of his previous five meetings with the Packers, St. Brown was held to under 57 receiving yards while furnishing his fourth-lowest yardage total of the campaign. However, he saved his most valuable contribution for his final catch, as he brought in a 16-yard dart from Jared Goff over the middle on second-and-17 with 1:42 remaining. Despite the modest numbers Thursday, St. Brown should be heavily involved in a Week 15 home matchup against the Bills on Sunday, Dec. 15 that could serve as a Super Bowl preview.</p> <h4 id="michael-pittman-jr-wr">Michael Pittman Jr. (WR)</h4> <p><strong>Injury Status:</strong> Active <br/> <strong>Lineup Slot:</strong> BE <br/> <strong>Details:</strong> Second-year QB Anthony Richardson completed only half of his 24 attempts, and Pittman was by far the Colts’ leader in catches and receiving yards as a result despite his modest numbers. Since missing a Week 10 contest with back trouble, Pittman has been his usual stalwart self, posting a 16-184-0 line on 22 targets over three contests, but his TD drought now sits at six games. He’ll look to find paydirt again on the other side of the Colts’ Week 14 bye,</p> <h4 id="trevor-lawrence-qb">Trevor Lawrence (QB)</h4> <p><strong>Injury Status:</strong> Injured Reserve <br/> <strong>Lineup Slot:</strong> IR <br/> <strong>Details:</strong> Regardless of the exact timing of surgery, Lawrence won’t play again this season and should have plenty of time to recover before Week 1 of 2025. It’s his left, non-throwing shoulder that will be operated on, which means there shouldn’t be much impact for next season even if the process is delayed a few weeks. Jacksonville’s roster and/or coaching staff may look very different by the time Lawrence is healthy.</p> <h4 id="quentin-johnston-wr">Quentin Johnston (WR)</h4> <p><strong>Injury Status:</strong> Active <br/> <strong>Lineup Slot:</strong> RB/WR/TE <br/> <strong>Details:</strong> Some assumed Johnston would operate as the team’s top target with Ladd McConkey (shoulder/knee) sidelined, but Joshua Palmer took over as the intermediate focal point (6-9-78). Johnston still nearly saw a season high in looks (he had eight back in Week 11), which is a prominent point especially because the second-year target was still used as a deep-threat specialist. Given the litany of difficult injuries McConkey seems to be trying to gut through, Johnston and Palmer could once again see an uptick in work against a bad Tampa Bay defense next week.</p> <h4 id="raheem-mostert-rb">Raheem Mostert (RB)</h4> <p><strong>Injury Status:</strong> Questionable <br/> <strong>Lineup Slot:</strong> BE <br/> <strong>Details:</strong> questionable</p> <h4 id="devin-singletary-rb">Devin Singletary (RB)</h4> <p><strong>Injury Status:</strong> Active <br/> <strong>Lineup Slot:</strong> RB <br/> <strong>Details:</strong> Singletary opened the campaign as New York’s starting running back, but he’s since given way to rookie Tyrone Tracy in the backfield. Tracy carried 16 times Sunday and was targeted 10 times, while Singletary was barely heard from with his two rushes, which went for four yards apiece. Given his increasingly limited opportunities, Singletary would likely need Tracy to miss time in order to be a viable fantasy asset again, even in deeper leagues.</p> <h4 id="aaron-rodgers-qb">Aaron Rodgers (QB)</h4> <p><strong>Injury Status:</strong> Active <br/> <strong>Lineup Slot:</strong> OP <br/> <strong>Details:</strong> Rodgers not only surpassed 200 passing yards for the first time since Week 9, but he exceeded 300 for the first time as a member of the Jets. He found Garrett Wilson for a 35-yard gain to convert on fourth down in the second quarter, setting up Isaiah Davis’ 17-yard touchdown run on the next play. Rodgers connected with Wilson again for a 42-yard pickup in the third quarter to set up Rodgers’ only touchdown pass of the afternoon – a three-yarder to Davante Adams. All told, Wilson and Adams combined for 223 of Rodgers’ 339 passing yards, but the Jets never got a chance to possess the ball in overtime as Miami drove down the field to drop New York’s record to 3-10. Barring an announcement to the contrary from the team, Rodgers will remain the starter in Week 15, when the Jets face the 3-10 Jaguars in a game with significant implications for the 2025 NFL Draft order.</p> <h4 id="russell-wilson-qb">Russell Wilson (QB)</h4> <p><strong>Injury Status:</strong> Active <br/> <strong>Lineup Slot:</strong> QB <br/> <strong>Details:</strong> Wilson started the game slowly as he had just 46 yards on 16 attempts at halftime. However, he led the Steelers on an eight-play, 67-yard touchdown drive that ended with a 10-yard pass to Van Jefferson on the team’s first offensive possession. One drive later, he took advantage of a short field and delivered a 20-yard score to Pat Freiermuth. This wasn’t Wilson’s most prolific performance, but he managed the offense well and threw for multiple scores for the fourth time in seven starts on the campaign.</p> <h4 id="tyler-lockett-wr">Tyler Lockett (WR)</h4> <p><strong>Injury Status:</strong> Active <br/> <strong>Lineup Slot:</strong> BE <br/> <strong>Details:</strong> Lockett couldn’t haul in an end-zone target, as Cardinals’ rookie CB Max Melton blanketed the veteran receiver. Since Week 7, Lockett has produced more than 20 receiving yards just once while Jaxon Smith-Njigba and DK Metcalf received a bulk of the targets. It will be difficult to trust Lockett in fantasy moving forward.</p> <h4 id="kenneth-walker-iii-rb">Kenneth Walker III (RB)</h4> <p><strong>Injury Status:</strong> Questionable <br/> <strong>Lineup Slot:</strong> BE <br/> <strong>Details:</strong> Macdonald added that Walker no longer is dealing with the ankle issue that, along with the calf concern, capped him to one limited session last week and kept him out of Sunday’s win at Arizona. The Seahawks will post their first practice report of Week 15 prep Wednesday, at which point his activity level may be telling for his chances to return to action this coming Sunday against the Packers. In Walker’s absence Week 14, Zach Charbonnet handled an 80 percent snap share and racked up 29 touches for 193 yards from scrimmage and two rushing TDs, while Kenny McIntosh earned 23 percent of snaps en route to nine touches for 45 total yards.</p> <h4 id="mike-evans-wr">Mike Evans (WR)</h4> <p><strong>Injury Status:</strong> Active <br/> <strong>Lineup Slot:</strong> WR <br/> <strong>Details:</strong> Evans tied Sterling Shepard and Jalen McMillan for the team lead in receptions while checking in second in receiving yards. The veteran wideout got a big chunk of his production on a 32-yard grab, which was the second longest of the game for the Buccaneers. Evans has eclipsed 60 receiving yards in three straight games heading into a Week 15 road battle against the Chargers.</p> <h2 id="current-lineup">Current Lineup</h2> <table data-click-to-select="true" data-height="630" data-search="false" data-toggle="table" data-url="/assets/json/team_rosters/Week_14_2024_TIB_roster.json"> <thead> <tr> <th data-field="player_name" data-halign="left" data-align="left" data-sortable="true">Player</th> <th data-field="pos" data-halign="center" data-align="center" data-sortable="true">Position</th> <th data-field="slot" data-halign="center" data-align="center" data-sortable="true">Slot</th> <th data-field="points" data-halign="center" data-align="center" data-sortable="true">Points</th> <th data-field="projected" data-halign="center" data-align="center" data-sortable="true">Projected</th> </tr> </thead> </table> <p><br/><br/></p> <h2 id="optimal-lineup">Optimal Lineup</h2> <table data-click-to-select="true" data-height="630" data-search="false" data-toggle="table" data-url="/assets/json/team_rosters/Week_14_2024_TIB_optimal.json"> <thead> <tr> <th data-field="player_name" data-halign="left" data-align="left" data-sortable="true">Player</th> <th data-field="pos" data-halign="center" data-align="center" data-sortable="true">Position</th> <th data-field="slot" data-halign="center" data-align="center" data-sortable="true">Slot</th> <th data-field="points" data-halign="center" data-align="center" data-sortable="true">Points</th> <th data-field="projected" data-halign="center" data-align="center" data-sortable="true">Projected</th> </tr> </thead> </table>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="team-reports"/><category term="2024-25,"/><category term="WeeklyRecap,"/><category term="Week14"/><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Weekly team status report]]></summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Tom and Jerry Week 14 Report</title><link href="https://family-fantasy-football.github.io/blog/2024/Week-14-TOM/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Tom and Jerry Week 14 Report"/><published>2024-12-10T22:19:38+00:00</published><updated>2024-12-10T22:19:38+00:00</updated><id>https://family-fantasy-football.github.io/blog/2024/Week-14-TOM</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://family-fantasy-football.github.io/blog/2024/Week-14-TOM/"><![CDATA[<h2 id="week-at-a-glance">Week at a Glance</h2> <p>Tom and Jerry Lost against Pink Pony Club 154.40-169.20<br/> Current Standing: #4<br/> Playoff Chances: 100.0%<br/> Lineup Efficiency: 86.4%<br/> Best Performer: Josh Jacobs (24.60 pts)<br/></p> <pre><code class="language-echarts">{
    "tooltip": {
        "trigger": "item",
        "formatter": "{a} &lt;br/&gt;{b}: {d}%"
    },
    "legend": {
        "orient": "vertical",
        "left": "left",
        "data": [
            "QB",
            "RB",
            "WR",
            "TE",
            "D/ST",
            "K"
        ]
    },
    "series": [
        {
            "name": "Position Points",
            "type": "pie",
            "radius": [
                "50%",
                "70%"
            ],
            "avoidLabelOverlap": false,
            "data": [
                {
                    "value": 33.1,
                    "name": "QB"
                },
                {
                    "value": 35.0,
                    "name": "RB"
                },
                {
                    "value": 62.8,
                    "name": "WR"
                },
                {
                    "value": 23.5,
                    "name": "TE"
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}
</code></pre> <h2 id="player-report">Player Report</h2> <h4 id="justice-hill-rb">Justice Hill (RB)</h4> <p><strong>Injury Status:</strong> Active <br/> <strong>Lineup Slot:</strong> BE <br/> <strong>Details:</strong> Hill saw his customary level of usage while working in a change-of-pace role behind Derrick Henry. Hill’s volume has been remarkably consistent heading into Baltimore’s Week 14 bye. He has totaled between six and eight touches nine times this season while falling short of six three times and exceeding eight just once, when Hill had four carries and six catches against the Bills back in Week 4.</p> <h4 id="jerome-ford-rb">Jerome Ford (RB)</h4> <p><strong>Injury Status:</strong> Active <br/> <strong>Lineup Slot:</strong> BE <br/> <strong>Details:</strong> Ford’s 13 touches were his most since coming back a hamstring injury in Week 9. He was on the field for 40 snaps, more than starter Nick Chubb (26) for the second consecutive game, but that has more to do with Cleveland playing from behind. The Browns have attempted more than 40 passes six times in the seven games since Jameis Winston has taken over at quarterback. That’s a situation that benefits Ford, who leads the backfield with 36 targets.</p> <h4 id="jerry-jeudy-wr">Jerry Jeudy (WR)</h4> <p><strong>Injury Status:</strong> Active <br/> <strong>Lineup Slot:</strong> RB/WR/TE <br/> <strong>Details:</strong> Jeudy couldn’t match his Week 13 explosion, but he remained productive with Jameis Winston under center. He began his performance with a long 35-yard touchdown catch after splitting the defense down the seam. While the Browns’ offense was stalled for much of the contest thereafter, Jeudy did manage to remain a reliable target. Jeudy has now topped 70 receiving yards and/or found the end zone in each of Winston’s six starts.</p> <h4 id="jake-ferguson-te">Jake Ferguson (TE)</h4> <p><strong>Injury Status:</strong> Active <br/> <strong>Lineup Slot:</strong> BE <br/> <strong>Details:</strong> Making his return from a two-game absence due to a concussion, Ferguson finished second in receptions, receiving yards and targets for the Cowboys on the night. Cooper Rush only threw for 183 yards overall, so Ferguson’s production was serviceable if unspectacular in that context. The promising tight end draws a favorable matchup in a Week 15 road clash with the Panthers.</p> <h4 id="tucker-kraft-te">Tucker Kraft (TE)</h4> <p><strong>Injury Status:</strong> Active <br/> <strong>Lineup Slot:</strong> RB/WR/TE <br/> <strong>Details:</strong> Kraft was second in receptions, tied for second in targets and was third in receiving yards for the Packers on a night when Jordan Love only completed 12 passes. The versatile tight end has demonstrated a knack for rattling off chunk plays throughout the season, and he recorded his sixth catch of 20-plus yards Thursday with a 21-yard grab. Kraft also tallied his career-high seventh touchdown on a 12-yard catch that capped off Green Bay’s first second-half drive, and he should have opportunities to make an impact again during a Week 15 road matchup against the Seahawks on Sunday night, Dec. 15.</p> <h4 id="jordan-love-qb">Jordan Love (QB)</h4> <p><strong>Injury Status:</strong> Active <br/> <strong>Lineup Slot:</strong> BE <br/> <strong>Details:</strong> Love averaged an impressive 10.3 yards per attempt, but he recorded his second-fewest number of pass attempts this season against a Lions squad that had forced opponents to the air plenty. With stalwart interior lineman DJ Reader (shoulder) sidelined and fellow defensive tackle Alim McNeill (head) exiting for the Lions early in the contest, the Packers were able to lean on Josh Jacobs on the ground about as much as usual, and Love was also the victim of Detroit’s 12-minute-plus time-of-possession advantage. His one touchdown pass went to Tucker Kraft from 12 yards out to cap off the first possession of the second half, a drive Love ignited with a 59-yard completion to Christian Watson. The fourth-year signal-caller does now have a three-game interception-less streak, and Love should be more active through the air in a key Week 15 road matchup against the Seahawks on Sunday night, Dec. 15.</p> <h4 id="josh-jacobs-rb">Josh Jacobs (RB)</h4> <p><strong>Injury Status:</strong> Active <br/> <strong>Lineup Slot:</strong> RB <br/> <strong>Details:</strong> Jacobs had a fourth touchdown via a six-yard reception nullified by an offensive pass interference penalty on Christian Watson with just under five minutes remaining in the game. The standout back found the end zone on the ground from one, six and four yards out in the second, third and fourth quarters, respectively, his second three-touchdown effort of the season. Jacobs also officially went without a catch for the third time overall in 2024, but his near complete domination of Green Bay’s backfield and his massive red-zone usage keeps him as an elite option in a Week 15 road matchup against the Seahawks on Sunday night, Dec. 15.</p> <h4 id="tank-dell-wr">Tank Dell (WR)</h4> <p><strong>Injury Status:</strong> Active <br/> <strong>Lineup Slot:</strong> BE <br/> <strong>Details:</strong> Dell recorded his sole catch early in the fourth quarter, a reflection of how unusually quiet the speedy second-year wideout’s afternoon was. Dell’s target total also tied a season low, and his yardage was his fewest since Week 8. The 2023 third-round pick will now have a Week 14 bye to rest up before resuming a quest to snap what is now a five-game touchdown drought at the expense of the Dolphins in a Week 15 home matchup Sunday, Dec. 15.</p> <h4 id="alec-pierce-wr">Alec Pierce (WR)</h4> <p><strong>Injury Status:</strong> Active <br/> <strong>Lineup Slot:</strong> BE <br/> <strong>Details:</strong> The third-year wideout dealt with a foot injury in practice this week, and while he was eventually cleared to play, Pierce appeared headed for a very quiet day until he caught a three-yard TD from Anthony Richardson with just 12 seconds left in the fourth quarter for what seemed to be the tying score. Rather than sending the game to overtime with an extra point though, coach Shane Steichen put the ball in Richardson’s hands, and the young QB ran in a two-point conversion for the win. The touchdown was Pierce’s fifth of the season after he managed only four across his first two NFL campaigns, and he’ll get a bye in Week 14 to let his foot heal further.</p> <h4 id="patrick-mahomes-qb">Patrick Mahomes (QB)</h4> <p><strong>Injury Status:</strong> Active <br/> <strong>Lineup Slot:</strong> QB <br/> <strong>Details:</strong> Mahomes put the Chiefs up 13-0 with a nine-yard touchdown pass to DeAndre Hopkins in the final minute of the first half, but the Chargers scored 14 unanswered points in the third quarter. The two teams then exchanged go-ahead field goals in the fourth quarter before Mahomes converted a pair of third downs with passes of 14 yards to Xavier Worthy and nine yards to Travis Kelce to set up Matthew Wright’s game-winning 31-yard field goal on the game’s final play. It hasn’t always been pretty offensively as Kansas City navigates subpar offensive line play with a depleted receiving corps, but Mahomes has led the Chiefs to a 12-1 record and an AFC West Division title heading into a Week 15 trip to Cleveland.</p> <h4 id="jonnu-smith-te">Jonnu Smith (TE)</h4> <p><strong>Injury Status:</strong> Active <br/> <strong>Lineup Slot:</strong> TE <br/> <strong>Details:</strong> Smith stepped up in overtime after being blanked in regulation. He caught consecutive screen passes for gains of 20 and 14 yards, then scored the game-winning touchdown on a 10-yard catch five plays later. This was Smith’s lowest yardage total since Week 8, but the surging tight end has 345 receiving yards and four touchdowns in his last four games. He’ll look to stay hot in Week 15 against the Texans.</p> <h4 id="alvin-kamara-rb">Alvin Kamara (RB)</h4> <p><strong>Injury Status:</strong> Active <br/> <strong>Lineup Slot:</strong> RB <br/> <strong>Details:</strong> The game was a slog for both offenses, and Kamara’s 44 rushing yards was his lowest total since Week 7. The star running back did catch at least four passes for the 10th straight game however, and his 64 receptions on the season leads all RBs, just ahead of De’Von Achane (63). Kamara is just 73 scrimmage yards short of reaching 1,500 for the fourth time in his career and the first time since 2020, and he needs 62 more rushing yards to hit 1,000 for the first time. He’ll take aim at both marks in Week 15 against the Commanders.</p> <h4 id="aj-brown-wr">A.J. Brown (WR)</h4> <p><strong>Injury Status:</strong> Active <br/> <strong>Lineup Slot:</strong> WR <br/> <strong>Details:</strong> The fifth-year wideout tied for his lowest target volume of the season, but Brown still led the Eagles in receiving yards on a day in which Jalen Hurts threw for just 108 yards. With Saquon Barkley clearly the focal point of the Philly offense, it’s become harder for Brown to make a big impact, and he’s scored only one TD over the last seven games while posting a 32-512-1 line on 42 targets. He’ll try to turn things around in Week 15 against the Steelers.</p> <h4 id="mike-williams-wr">Mike Williams (WR)</h4> <p><strong>Injury Status:</strong> Active <br/> <strong>Lineup Slot:</strong> BE <br/> <strong>Details:</strong> The Steelers had limited pass volume, with Russell Wilson taking to the air only 26 times. Even with an expanded role in the absence of George Pickens (groin), that led to a modest stat line for Williams. Nevertheless, it was his best usage as a Steeler, and he finished tied for second on the team in targets. Even with some slight reason for optimism, it’s difficult to trust that Williams will post a meaningful stat line heading into a Week 15 matchup against the Eagles.</p> <h4 id="jauan-jennings-wr">Jauan Jennings (WR)</h4> <p><strong>Injury Status:</strong> Active <br/> <strong>Lineup Slot:</strong> WR <br/> <strong>Details:</strong> George Kittle led the 49ers in receiving yards (151) Sunday while Jennings took top honors in catches, targets and receiving touchdowns. The 27-year-old wideout continues to excel in a starting role for a San Francisco team that has lost several key players over the course of the season. Jennings is having a breakout season with a career-best line of 57-774-6 through 11 contests. He will attempt to build on those numbers in a potential high-scoring affair against the Rams on Thursday Night Football in Week 15.</p> <h4 id="jaxon-smith-njigba-wr">Jaxon Smith-Njigba (WR)</h4> <p><strong>Injury Status:</strong> Active <br/> <strong>Lineup Slot:</strong> WR <br/> <strong>Details:</strong> Smith-Njigba finished as the Seahawks’ leading receiver despite finishing third in targets Sunday. The budding sophomore cashed in Seattle’s lone passing touchdown while setting a new high in season scores (five). Smith-Njigba has been white-hot in the second half of the schedule, averaging yards 101.5 yards from scrimmage with four total touchdowns over his last six contests. Fantasy managers should feel confident starting JSN as the Seahawks prepare to face the Packers next Sunday.</p> <h4 id="baker-mayfield-qb">Baker Mayfield (QB)</h4> <p><strong>Injury Status:</strong> Active <br/> <strong>Lineup Slot:</strong> OP <br/> <strong>Details:</strong> Mayfield ultimately finished with an impressive yardage and touchdown total, but his road to those numbers was rocky at times. The veteran signal-caller took four sacks from an aggressive Raiders defense and tossed a pair of first-half interceptions following a fast start. Prior to the miscues, Mayfield had capped off the Buccaneers’ first two drives with touchdown passes to Jalen McMillan (15 yards) and Rachaad White (five yards). He also came on late after Tampa Bay’s first two second-half drives ended in punts, capping off a five-play game-sealing drive with a 29-yard scoring strike to McMillan. Mayfield does have four interceptions over his last two games, but he’s also tossed four touchdowns in that span going into a Week 15 road matchup against the Chargers.</p> <h4 id="austin-ekeler-rb">Austin Ekeler (RB)</h4> <p><strong>Injury Status:</strong> Injured Reserve <br/> <strong>Lineup Slot:</strong> BE <br/> <strong>Details:</strong> Ekeler said he doesn’t remember walking off the field Nov. 24 against the Cowboys, or indeed anything until he got in the ambulance to go to the hospital. The veteran running back also states he had memory loss following his Week 3 concussion earlier in the season. All of these symptoms led to Ekeler’s placement on injured reserve ahead of Week 13, sidelining him until at least Week 18. Brian Robinson, Jeremy McNichols and Chris Rodriguez are set to handle backfield duties while Ekeler is out.</p> <h2 id="current-lineup">Current Lineup</h2> <table data-click-to-select="true" data-height="630" data-search="false" data-toggle="table" data-url="/assets/json/team_rosters/Week_14_2024_TOM_roster.json"> <thead> <tr> <th data-field="player_name" data-halign="left" data-align="left" data-sortable="true">Player</th> <th data-field="pos" data-halign="center" data-align="center" data-sortable="true">Position</th> <th data-field="slot" data-halign="center" data-align="center" data-sortable="true">Slot</th> <th data-field="points" data-halign="center" data-align="center" data-sortable="true">Points</th> <th data-field="projected" data-halign="center" data-align="center" data-sortable="true">Projected</th> </tr> </thead> </table> <p><br/><br/></p> <h2 id="optimal-lineup">Optimal Lineup</h2> <table data-click-to-select="true" data-height="630" data-search="false" data-toggle="table" data-url="/assets/json/team_rosters/Week_14_2024_TOM_optimal.json"> <thead> <tr> <th data-field="player_name" data-halign="left" data-align="left" data-sortable="true">Player</th> <th data-field="pos" data-halign="center" data-align="center" data-sortable="true">Position</th> <th data-field="slot" data-halign="center" data-align="center" data-sortable="true">Slot</th> <th data-field="points" data-halign="center" data-align="center" data-sortable="true">Points</th> <th data-field="projected" data-halign="center" data-align="center" data-sortable="true">Projected</th> </tr> </thead> </table>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="team-reports"/><category term="2024-25,"/><category term="WeeklyRecap,"/><category term="Week14"/><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Weekly team status report]]></summary></entry></feed>